Good night, everyone, the speech is about to begin
おやすみ、皆さん、演説が始まります
Please set your phone to vibrate or silent
携帯電話を振動またはサイレントに設定してください
Please do not use the flash to take pictures during the speech
講演中のフラッシュ撮影はご遠慮ください
Thanks
ありがとう
To make our lectures better
講義をより良いものにするために
Welcome everyone after the speech
スピーチの後は皆さん歓迎します
Help us scan the QR Code of the award dealer
特典ディーラーのQRコードのスキャンにご協力ください。
Fill out our big questionnaire
大きなアンケートに記入してください
After the end at the reception desk outside the venue
終了後会場外受付にて
There will be a small gift, thank you
ちょっとしたプレゼントもございます、よろしくお願いします
Academia Sinica's 111-year Knowledge Feast
中央研究院111年知識饗宴
Dean Hu Shi's lecture begins
胡詩学部長の講義が始まります
before the speech
スピーチの前に
Let us first ask the director-general of the China Education and Culture Foundation
まず中国教育文化基金会の局長にお聞きします。
Mr. Wang Jianya awarded us the 110th annual
王建雅氏より第110回記念賞を授与されました
Hu Shi Memorial Research Award
胡施記念研究賞
please the winner is also the speaker tonight
勝者が今夜のスピーカーでもありますのでお願いします
Institute of Waiting History
待機歴史研究所
Wu Renshu, a researcher, came to the stage to accept the award
研究者の呉仁秀氏が授賞式に登壇
and a group photo
そして集合写真
Thanks
ありがとう
Then we also asked Vice President Huang to take a group photo with us
その後、黄副総統にも集合写真を撮ってもらいました。
This is a very big book cage for a very important person of the year social sciences
これは社会科学の今年の非常に重要な人物のための非常に大きな本かごです
Congratulations to Mr. Wu, please go back to your seat first
ウーさん、おめでとうございます。先に席に戻ってください。
Let's first invite Mr. Wang Jianya, the secretary-general of the China Golden Crystal Association, to give us a speech
まずは中国金水晶協会事務局長の王建雅氏にご講演をお願いいたします。
Vice President Huang Researcher Wu Academia Sinica
黄副院長 呉研究員 中央研究院
Colleagues from the highest academic unit, hello everyone
最高学府の同僚の皆さん、こんにちは。
Hello everyone
こんにちは、みんな
This Hu Shi Foundation was established in the 54th year of the Republic of China
この胡施財団は中華民国54年に設立されました。
so look at him
だから彼を見てください
It's almost 60 years now
もう60年近く経つんですね
However, this 60-year
しかし、この60年間、
The words of the China Education and Culture Foundation
中国教育文化財団の言葉
We're almost 100 years old so in short
私たちはもうすぐ100歳になるので、要するに
Let me introduce the China Education and Culture Foundation
中国教育文化基金会についてご紹介します。
It's about following the payout
賠償のフォローアップです
It was during the Manchu Qing Dynasty that the Eight-Power Allied Forces
八カ国連合軍が発足したのは満州清朝の時代であった。
attack the party
パーティーを攻撃する
to this
これに
When the city of Beijing burned down in the Yuan and Ming Dynasties
元・明の時代に北京市が焼失したとき
So the Eight-Power Allied Forces paid compensation to Zi at that time
そのため、八国連合軍は当時Ziに賠償金を支払った
At that time, the whole of China had about 400 million people.
当時、中国全土の人口は約4億人でした。
At that time, it was 10,000,000, 40,000,000
当時は1000万、4000万だった
40,000,000, then each person will pay one or two yuan
4000万なら一人当たり1～2元払うことになる
So it's 40,000 taels
つまり40,000テイルです
Your history should be very clear
あなたの履歴は非常に明確である必要があります
After the compensation, of course there will be some military expenses.
賠償金の後には当然軍事費も発生します。
The military expenditure of the Eight-Nation Allied Forces, these many blessings
八ヶ国連合軍の軍事費、その数々の恩恵
at that time so
その時はそう
When the government at that time was negotiating with the United States
当時の政府がアメリカと交渉していたとき
of course
もちろん
The other eight coalitions France Germany
他の8つの連合 フランス ドイツ
There are also blessings
祝福もあります
But the United States they admit
しかし、彼らが認めている米国
These are more parts of the blessing
これらは祝福のさらなる部分です
returned to the government at that time
当時の政府に戻った
So about ten million
それで1000万くらい
More than ten million dollars, that's a lot
1000万ドル以上ってすごいですね
a lot of money
たくさんのお金
but at that time it was a
しかし当時は
Under the situation of warlord separatism
軍閥分離の状況下で
So at that time the U.S. government decided to establish
そこで当時米国政府は、
Chinese Education and Culture Foundation
中国教育文化財団
is an independent foundation
独立した財団です
the president at that time
当時の社長
maybe you should all know
たぶん皆さんは知っているはずです
It's President Cao Kun
曹昆総統です
So our China Education and Culture Foundation
それで、私たちの中国教育文化財団
The mid-term meeting was established in the 24th year of the Republic of China
中間会議は民国24年に設立されました。
we still have
私たちはまだ持っています
President Cao Kun
曹昆総統
Seal established
シール確立
In the 24th year of the Republic of China, with Academia Sinica
民国24年、中央研究院と
It's a little late for us
私たちには少し遅れています
Academia Sinica is the 28th year of the Republic of China
中央研究院は中華民国建国28年目です
It burned us for four years
それは私たちを4年間燃やしました
So we are in two years
それで2年後です
just a hundred years
ちょうど百年
that is
あれは
Republic of China
中華民国
first foundation
最初の財団
a hundred years in two years
二年で百年
In fact, this hundred years
実はこの百年、
We do very, very much especially in
私たちは特に以下の分野で非常に多くのことを行っています
in the early days because it was
初期の頃はそうだったので
The dollar is very small so we
ドルは非常に小さいので、
Using these we've sponsored so many
これらを使用して、私たちは非常に多くのスポンサーを務めてきました
Because I was going abroad
海外に行くことになったので
do whatever you want to do conference
カンファレンスでやりたいことは何でもやる
the equipment you want
欲しい装備
all in dollars so we
すべてドルなので、私たちは
During these hundred years
この百年の間に
In fact, it has been
実際、それは行われてきました
Talk to all our academic units
すべての学術部門と話し合ってください
From various institutes of Academia Sinica
中央研究院のさまざまな研究機関から
And we communicated with Qingda
そして私たちは青達と通信しました
Academic units have a lot of cooperation
学術部門は多くの協力を行っています
Then we have a lot of cooperation with Academia Sinica
その後、中央研究院と多くの協力を行っています。
right now in this
今この中で
Hu Foundation
胡財団
Currently 60 years
現在60歳
still we uphold the same
それでも私たちは同じことを守ります
The original intention almost 100 years ago
当初の目的は約100年前
We want to be an independent
私たちは独立したいのです
Education and Culture Foundation
教育文化財団
Can help all education in Taiwan
台湾のあらゆる教育に貢献できます
With the development of various cultural projects
様々な文化事業を展開しながら
In addition to what the government can do
政府ができること以外にも
Of course now the government
もちろん今では政府が
May be right for Chinese culture
中国文化には合っているかもしれない
This promotion is not so much
このプロモーションはそれほど多くありません
then our foundation
それから私たちの財団
Will do more Chinese culture
もっと中国文化をやります
This is 100 years ago
これは100年前のことです
98 years ago, our Central Accounting Association was founded
98年前、私たちの中央会計協会が設立されました
terminate us till now
今まで私たちを終了させて​​ください
have not changed
変わっていない
we will keep doing it
私たちはそれを続けます
Let me introduce it like this
こんな感じで紹介していきます
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
grateful
感謝
Thank you, Director Wang
王監督、ありがとうございました
Now we have Vice President Huang
黄副総統が登場しました
Host today's interview for us
今日のインタビューを司会してください
today's speech
今日のスピーチ
this
これ
Mayor Wang Gan who hit the position
役職に就いた王幹市長
The one who entered the market today's keynote speaker
市場参入者 本日の基調講演者
Professor Wu Renshu
吳仁樹教授
And distinguished guests, it's quite cold today
そしてご来賓の皆様、今日はとても寒いですね
So everyone listening to speeches in cold weather
寒い中スピーチを聞いている皆さん
is good to enjoy
楽しむのは良いことです
And Professor Wang's speech must be very exciting
王教授のスピーチはとても刺激的でしょう
Actually he is us
実は彼は私たちなのです
In China, social economy in the Ming and Qing Dynasties
中国における明・清時代の社会経済
a famous person in history
歴史上の有名人
In fact, many listeners also know him
実際、多くのリスナーも彼を知っています
He has written quite a lot
彼はかなりたくさんのことを書いています
and it's exciting
そしてそれは刺激的です
Especially the information he used
特に彼が使用した情報
are very omnivorous
非常に雑食性です
And delicate things like this
そしてこんな繊細なものも
Then his speech today
それから今日の彼のスピーチ
history
歴史
combined with this criminology
この犯罪学と組み合わせると
to give an explanation
説明をする
this is not easy
これは簡単ではありません
But in terms of his eloquence
しかし、彼の雄弁さという点では、
must be very exciting
とてもエキサイティングなはずです
There is one today, can you wait and see?
今日は1つありますが、待っていていただけますか？
It's Xier's court
ここはXierの法廷だ
then i won't say anything
それなら何も言いません
I hope we invite Professor Wu to give us a lecture
呉先生をお招きして講演していただければと思います
Thanks
ありがとう
Vice President Huang Director Wang Distinguished Guests
黄副社長 王取締役 来賓の皆様
Hope you all have a great night tonight
今夜は皆さんが素晴らしい夜をお過ごしください
Well, I am very honored to be the speaker of Hu Shi's lecture today
さて、今日は胡施氏の講演をさせていただくことを大変光栄に思います
Then I am even more honored to be able to receive from Director Wang
そして王監督からお言葉をいただけることがさらに光栄です
Get this very memorable lecture
とても思い出に残る講義を受講してください
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
In fact, the Central Product Association is not only a unit with a long history
実は中央物産協会は歴史ある団体だけではありません
At the same time, he has made great contributions to the academic and educational aspects of modern China.
同時に、現代中国の学術・教育面にも多大な貢献を果たした。
play a very important role
非常に重要な役割を果たします
I recently studied the modern Chinese agricultural students in this ruler
私は最近この定規で現代中国の農業学生を研究しました
You can still see that Zhongji will be inside
Zhongji が中にいることはまだわかります。
Support many Chinese international students to study abroad
多くの中国人留学生の留学をサポート
So I see this kind of material and feel it myself
だから私はこの種の資料を見て、自分自身でそれを感じます
It is a great honor to receive this award
この賞を受賞できて大変光栄です
Everyone knows the biggest dark horse in this year's World Cup
今年のワールドカップ最大のダークホースは誰もが知っている
It's Morocco, he made it to the semi-finals
モロッコだ、彼は準決勝まで進んだ
His coach once said a word
彼のコーチはかつてこう言った
He said as long as you have faith
彼は言った、「信仰がある限り」
Achievement without talent
才能のない成果
I always thought I had no talent
ずっと自分には才能がないと思っていた
no genius
天才じゃない
But I am very happy to be recognized by this award this time
でも、今回このような賞をいただけてとても嬉しいです
Then I will keep working hard
それではこれからも頑張ります
create better books
より良い本を作る
To repay the attention you have given me
あなたが私に与えてくれた注意に報いるために
Then because time is limited
それでは時間が限られているので
I'll go straight to our topic
早速本題に行きます
Well, what I want to introduce to you today is
さて、今日ご紹介したいのは、
Actually it was me recently
実は最近の私です
One of my students just finished a book
私の生徒の一人がちょうど本を読み終えたところです
The content of this book is to discuss
この本の内容は、
the crime of the mid-nineteenth century
19世紀半ばの犯罪
especially the problem of theft
特に盗難の問題
So I want to say that in this speech
だからこのスピーチで言いたいのは、
I especially focus on history and criminology
特に歴史と犯罪学に重点を置いています
how to meet
会う方法
How the two research methods fit together
2 つの研究方法がどのように組み合わされるか
to explore the question of criminal history
犯罪歴の問題を探求する
This picture is very interesting
この写真はとても興味深いです
It was painted in the nineteenth century
19世紀に描かれたものです
When Westerners came to China
西洋人が中国に来たとき
An image painted about the outside of Chongqing City
重慶市の郊外を描いた絵
Next we will enter
次に入ります
and record it in the content of the speech
そしてそれをスピーチの内容に記録します
As far as the discussion is concerned, the eight counties in Sichuan
議論に関する限り、四川省の 8 県は
That is the place in Chongqing now as an example
それは例として今の重慶の場所です
Let me tell a story first
まず話をさせてください
in the Ming and Qing Dynasties
明と清の時代に
Especially in the novels of the Ming Dynasty
特に明代の小説では
There is a famous Shinto
有名な神社があります
also has a supernatural power
超自然的な力も持っています
Also known as Chivalry
騎士道とも呼ばれる
called an eyebrow
眉毛と呼ばれる
Then according to the second subject of the novel, send the reporter
次に、小説の 2 番目の主題に従って、記者を送ります
Feng Rongrong described
フェン・ロンロンの説明
Yimei is a person in the middle of the family
イーメイは家族の真ん中にいる人です
He lives in an alley near Xuanmiao Pot in Suzhou
彼は蘇州の玄妙壷近くの路地に住んでいます
Dyed Dragon
ダイドドラゴン
every time he succeeds in a
彼が何かに成功するたびに
after stealing
盗んだ後
He will draw an eyebrow flower on the wall
彼は壁に眉毛の花を描くでしょう
draw an eyebrow
眉毛を描く
So he called it an eyebrow
それで彼はそれを眉毛と呼んだ
Then the illustrations in this novel
そして、この小説の挿絵は、
just drew an eyebrow
眉毛を描いただけです
However, this illustration
しかし、このイラストは
Everyone knows that in this Chinese painting
この中国の絵画では誰もがそれを知っています
This freehand brushwork is better than realism
このフリーハンドの筆致は写実よりも優れています
So everyone look carefully
だからみんなよく見てね
If you don't look carefully, you can't see it
よく見ないと見えないよ
this is a plum
これは梅です
I always feel that it seems to be painting a pot
いつも鍋に絵を描いているような気がする
Then this is freehand words
それでは、これはフリーハンドの言葉です
Then the Godhead Will Mei described here
そして、ここで説明されている神の神ウィル・メイは、
it's very powerful
それはとても強力です
seems to have light work
軽い仕事をしているようです
so it can jump on roofs
屋根の上にジャンプできるように
it can touch the wall
壁に触れるかもしれない
Coming and going like ghosts and gods coming and going like wind and rain
幽霊のように行ったり来たり、風や雨のように神が行ったり来たり
more interesting is
もっと興味深いのは
The things it stole are Tibetan art materials
盗んだものはチベット画材
What it stole was distributed to many civilians
盗んだものは多くの民間人に配布された
So in this novel
そこでこの小説では
Admit it is the world's first thief
世界初の泥棒だと認める
It describes the things it steals
盗むものについて説明します
including its chivalrous behavior
その騎士道的な振る舞いも含めて
It sometimes steals deposits from big businessmen
時には大実業家から預金を盗むこともある
Sometimes they steal the business of the fourth generation of Fu's family
時々、彼らはフーの家族の 4 世代目のビジネスを盗みます。
after stealing
盗んだ後
It distributes these operations to civilians
これらの作戦を民間人に分散させる
It will also describe
についても説明します
it always misses when it steals
盗むときはいつも逃す
Sometimes it just happens to be bumped into
たまたまぶつかってしまうこともある
so how does it get away
それでどうやって逃げるのですか
Sometimes when saplings go to this imitation house to steal silver taels
時々苗木が銀の尾を盗むためにこの模造家に行くとき
Happened to be locked inside his robe cabinet.
偶然、彼のローブキャビネットの中に閉じ込められていました。
He just figured out how to get out
彼はちょうど抜け出す方法を見つけたところだ
He will pretend to be a mouse sound
彼はネズミの音のふりをするでしょう
Such family members think that
そんな家族はこう思う
There are mice in his robe
彼のローブにはネズミがいる
not open
開いていません
he rushed out
彼は飛び出した
take this opportunity to escape
この機会に逃げてください
You can also see this sapling
こんな苗木も見られます
He steals clothes from this clothes store
彼はこの衣料品店から服を盗みます
You can see this kind of light
こんな光が見えるんだ
chase him at last
ついに彼を追いかける
Then find a way when he escapes
それから彼が逃げるときに方法を見つけてください
just lost a burden
ただ重荷を失っただけ
Everyone stopped chasing him because of the burden
負担のせいで誰もが彼を追うのをやめた
Just look at what's in the bag
バッグの中に何が入っているか見てみましょう
So
それで
In addition, we also saw that the story described
さらに、説明されているストーリーもわかります。
this one seedling
この苗一本
He is famous because of his godhead
彼はその神格のゆえに有名である
So many people want to bet with him
とても多くの人が彼と賭けたいと思っています
Said you have the ability to steal something from my house
あなたは私の家から何かを盗む能力があると言った
try it
それを試してみてください
Including the bet he had with the commander's family
指揮官の家族との賭けも含めて
He bet against the gambler
彼はギャンブラーに賭けた
And he bet against Jiujiaweng
そして彼は九家旺に賭けた
In the end, even with the same strong defense
結局、同じ強力な守備でも
In the end, they couldn't escape from the hands of the thief Ichimae.
結局、彼らは怪盗・市前の手から逃れることはできなかった。
So this is the magical situation that describes how he steals
これが彼がどのように盗むかを説明する魔法のような状況です
Sometimes he also teases some people
時々彼は人をからかうこともあります
To tease, for example, the son who likes to show off his wealth
たとえば、自分の富を見せびらかすのが好きな息子をからかうために
He put the vigilante's quilt in this boat
彼は自警団員のキルトをこのボートに置いた
Sometimes he also teases the priest
時々彼は神父をからかうこともある
This Taoist is unrepentant
この道士は悔い改めない
The most popular hat at the time with the swing cap
当時最も人気のあるスイングキャップ付きの帽子
go sightseeing
観光に行く
He just secretly changed the Taoist hat
彼は密かに道教の帽子を変えただけです
let these priests play
これらの司祭たちに遊ばせてください
Also he has an interesting story
さらに彼には興味深い話がある
It's the reflection of him helping a corrupt official to steal the censor
それは彼が腐敗した役人が検閲官を盗むのを手助けしたことの反映だ
Although after unsuccessful stealing
盗みに失敗した後ですが
This Yizhimei still persuades this current official to say
この宜志梅は今でもこの現役人を説得してこう言う。
you still put this
あなたはまだこれを置いています
Guan Ying returned it to Xu Anyi Shi
関英はそれを徐安義師に返した。
Because Xu An Yishi is a smart man
Xu An Yishi は賢い人だから
is a parent
親です
if you don't pay him back
あなたが彼に返済しなかったら
Maybe Xu Anyishi will be even more unfavorable to you in the end
おそらく徐安石は最終的にはあなたにとってさらに不利になるでしょう
But this Zixian didn't listen to him
しかし、このZixianは彼の言うことを聞きませんでした
But then the story is very interesting
でもその話はとても面白いです
Because Xu An Yishi is not the real story of Shen You
徐安義士は沈游の実話ではないからです
He thought of a way
彼はある方法を考えた
After he found out his official screening had been stolen
公式上映作品が盗まれていたことを知った後
He specially invited Zixian to his home for dinner
彼は特別にZixianを自宅に夕食に招待した
In the process of eating, there was a sudden fire
食事中に突然火災が発生しました
When there was a fire, he took the Guanying shell
火事が起こったとき、彼は観音貝を手に取りました
Empty shell
抜け殻
Just pretend to be the shell of the official movie
公式映画の抜け殻のふりをするだけ
Give it to Zixian
ジシエンにあげて
you keep it for me
あなたは私のためにそれを保管してください
keep it for me
私のために取っておいてください
You take it back and keep it for me
あなたはそれを取り戻して私のために保管してください
I'm going to fight the fire
消火活動に行くよ
This Zixian returned home with an empty Guanying shell
この子仙は空の観音貝殻を持って家に帰りました
just want to say no
ただノーと言いたいだけです
i stole his official movie
彼の公式ムービーを盗みました
Now he's giving me the empty shell
今彼は私に空っぽの殻をくれた
If I don't put the official screening back
公式上映を戻さないと
He took it and saw the empty shell
彼はそれを手に取り、空っぽの殻を見ました
He said I stole it
彼は私がそれを盗んだと言った
what to do with this hand
この手をどうするか
He had no choice but to put the official movie back obediently.
素直に公式ムービーを元に戻すしかなかった。
that empty box
その空箱
Xu Anyi got this
Xu Anyiはこれを受け取りました
Vis empty box see
空の箱を参照してください
about being in
入っていることについて
Of course there is plenty of luggage
もちろん荷物もたっぷり入ります
good guy
いいやつ
It's because your branch line is expensive.
支線の料金が高いからだ。
Sure enough, after Xu Anyi found out about this situation,
案の定、Xu Anyiはこの状況を知った後、
think of a way right away
すぐに方法を考える
turn off this soup
このスープを止めてください
This of course this is an interesting one about
もちろん、これは興味深いことです
this heroic story
この英雄的な物語
But in this story
しかし、この物語では
we clearly know
私たちははっきりと知っています
A lot of this story is pieced together
この物語の多くはひとつにまとまっている
how do you put it together
どうやってまとめますか
The most obvious is
最も明白なのは
He is capable of stealing a house
彼は家を盗むことができる
The one who stole the silver from this generation's father's house
今代の父の家から銀を盗んだ者
Then why is he still stealing clothes?
では、なぜ彼はまだ服を盗むのでしょうか？
Stealing clothes from these clothes shops?
洋服屋から服を盗むのですか？
That is to say
つまり
which example
どの例ですか
If there is a thief today
もし今日泥棒がいたら
Already capable of stealing bank vaults
すでに銀行の金庫室を盗む能力がある
But why is he going to UNICORO to steal clothes?
しかしなぜ彼はユニコロに服を盗みに行くのでしょうか？
so in this story
だからこの話では
Of course, a lot of them are pieced together.
もちろん、それらの多くは組み合わされています。
but is there such a person
でもそんな人いるの？
do you have an eyebrow
眉毛はありますか
Until now
今まで
Many scholars have not verified
多くの学者は検証していない
But I just found out
でも今知った
Yizhimei does have this person
Yizhimeiにはこの人がいます
And this person is in Yongzhou Prefecture, Hunan Province
そしてこの人は湖南省永州県にいます
he is an avenue
彼は大通りだ
Then he was cured by an official
その後、役人によって治癒されました
So left this record at that time
だからあの時の記録を残した
So this Yizhimei is indeed someone
つまり、このYizhimeiは確かに誰かです
but he is not a thief
しかし彼は泥棒ではありません
he is not a thief
彼は泥棒ではありません
he is an avenue
彼は大通りだ
But let's come back and talk about this issue
でも、戻ってこの問題について話しましょう
the study of criminal history
犯罪史の研究
In fact, the aspect of our past historical research
実際、私たちのこれまでの歴史研究の側面は、
getting bigger and bigger
どんどん大きくなる
But the study of criminal history itself
しかし、犯罪史の研究自体は
but for a long time
しかし長い間
arguably underappreciated or ignored
おそらく過小評価されているか無視されている
Of course there are several reasons
もちろん理由はいくつかあるのですが、
Because most of the historiography
なぜなら、歴史学のほとんどは、
To focus more on big events
大きなイベントにもっと集中するには
The outcome of major events in history
歴史上の大きな出来事の結果
such as war, revolution
戦争や革命など
For example, the war of the Taiping Heavenly Kingdom
例えば、太平天国戦争。
Xinhai Revolution
辛亥革命
and the daytime rebellion
そして昼の反乱
Even local food looting riots
地元の食料略奪暴動も
these are historians past
彼らは過去の歴史家です
very careful things
とても慎重なこと
But about some everyday crimes
でも日常的な犯罪については
something like a thief
泥棒のようなもの
In fact, historians have
実際、歴史家は、
I don't pay much attention to this research
この研究にはあまり注目していない
Of course not too much research
もちろんあまり研究しすぎないでください
There is another reason
別の理由があります
Issues involving so-called historical materials
いわゆる史料に関する問題
The so-called cleverness is hard to come by without rice
いわゆる賢さは米なしでは得られない
as a historical research
歴史研究として
you still have to have history
あなたにはまだ歴史が必要です
then it's a pity
それなら残念だ
History about this theft
この盗難に関する経緯
like we mentioned
先ほども言ったように
There are some descriptions in the novel notebook novel
小説ノート小説に一部記載あり
Then there are some descriptions in the koan novel
それから公案小説にもいくつかの記述があります。
Interpretation is some
解釈は多少なりとも
In these interpretations left by generations of husbands
何世代にもわたる夫によって残されたこれらの解釈では
There are also some descriptions
いくつかの説明もあります
But these are sporadic and not enough
しかし、これらは散発的で十分ではありません
We can't see a whole
全体が見えない
Holistic aspect of stealing
窃盗の全体的な側面
Well, again, the development of history in the past 20 years
さて、もう一度、過去 20 年間の歴史の発展
Especially the history of Ming and Qing Dynasties
特に明と清の歴史
Especially during the history of the Qing Dynasty
特に清朝の歴史においては
China has archives of many prefectures, counties and local counties
中国には多くの県、県、地方郡のアーカイブがある
was excavated
発掘されました
still very complete
まだ非常に完成度の高い
in these judicial files
これらの司法ファイルでは
preserve quite a few of these cases of theft.
これらの盗難事件はかなりの数残っています。
so that we historians can study
私たち歴史家が研究できるように
Of course when researching
研究するときはもちろん
We also hope that there will be a breakthrough in the method
また、この方法にブレークスルーがあることを期待しています。
So in the study of history in the past
それで、過去の歴史の勉強では
In fact, about the legal system
実は法制度に関しては
Social Phenomena Reflected by Law
法律が反映する社会現象
Such studies are more common in the past
このような研究は過去にはもっと一般的でした
But now if we want to focus on
しかし今、私たちが焦点を当てたいのであれば、
when moving to criminal history
犯罪歴に移るとき
we need to update the method
メソッドを更新する必要があります
which i think
私はそう思います
We can combine the so-called
いわゆるを組み合わせることができます
Criminology and History
犯罪学と歴史
That's what I'm talking about today
それが今日私が話していることです
Historical criminology is a new direction to do research
歴史犯罪学は研究の新しい方向性です
then the history of the past
それから過去の歴史
we just mentioned
先ほど言いました
Pay attention to historical events
歴史上の出来事に注目
Also pay attention to changes in some social structures
一部の社会構造の変化にも注目
legal system
法制度も重視
also pay attention to
也重視
litigation process
訴訟過程
aka police
別名警察
such a system
そのようなシステム
this is us historians past
これは私たち歴史家の過去です
more often noticed
気づくことが多くなった
criminology
犯罪学
its angle
その角度
Let's have some more interesting history
もっと面白い歴史を見てみましょう
Aspects of development neglected
開発の側面が無視されている
Except social change is the past
社会の変化が過去であることを除けば
everyone has been
誰もがそうしてきた
whether history or criminology
歴史でも犯罪学でも
other than the important issues that everyone will pay attention to
誰もが注目する重要な問題以外
then the cause of the crime
じゃあ犯行の原因は
Also discussed in criminal psychology
犯罪心理学でも議論される
perpetrator's motive
犯人の動機
criminal psychology
犯罪心理学
in criminology
犯罪学で
Discuss how to prevent crime
犯罪を防ぐ方法を話し合う
how to avoid crime
犯罪を避ける方法
And these angles and this orientation
そして、これらの角度とこの方向
but our history of the past
しかし、私たちの過去の歴史
less noticeable
目立たない
so we can try
それで試してみることができます
Using research methods from these two disciplines
これら 2 つの分野の研究手法を使用する
combine together
一緒に組み合わせる
let's have some new discussions
新しい議論をしましょう
what about here
ここはどうですか
I will commit crimes by cutting
切断して犯罪を犯します
discuss as an example
例として議論する
So what's the point of cutting to crime?
それでは、犯罪に手を染めることに何の意味があるのでしょうか？
How to do research
研究のやり方
First of all, we all feel that
まず、誰もが感じていることですが、
there are all kinds of crime
あらゆる種類の犯罪があります
So what does it matter when it comes to crime?
では、犯罪に関しては何が重要なのでしょうか？
Next, I will use the eight-line file
次に、8 行のファイルを使用します。
As you can see in the example of the eight-line file
8 行のファイルの例からわかるように、
This is all the eight line files
これは 8 行のファイルすべてです
From Qianlong tide to Xuantong tide
乾隆潮から玄通潮まで
according to its category
そのカテゴリーに応じて
The statistics of these numbers
これらの数字の統計
Then we can see from here
じゃあここからも見えるよ
cut to this class
このクラスにカット
cut to this class in the middle
途中でこのクラスにカット
It is the largest number of almost every trendy bag
ほぼすべてのトレンドバッグの最大数です
The biggest amount
最大の金額
Especially as I am now discussing the middle of the 19th century
特に私は今 19 世紀半ばについて話しています。
also when homosexuality
同性愛のときも
You see it has more than 3,000 pieces
3,000以上の作品があることがわかります
That comrade is only ten years old
あの仲間はまだ10歳だ
you average
あなたは平均的です
About 200 cases a year
年間約200件
I feel very sympathetic at this time
この時はとても共感しました
gay tide at that time
当時のゲイ潮流
Why is he restricting the limit?
なぜ彼は制限を設けているのでしょうか？
Every year he light theft
毎年彼は窃盗を軽視する
He will try more than 200 cases
彼は200以上の事件を試みるだろう
it's still theft
それはまだ盗難です
He has other cases to be sentenced
彼には他にも判決が下される事件がある
So the former constituency
つまり、以前の選挙区は
Especially in the mid-19th century of the Qing Dynasty
特に19世紀半ばの清朝では
Constitutional Officer of the Qing Dynasty
清朝の憲政官
really busy
本当に忙しい
For those constitutional officials at that time
当時の憲法当局者にとって
120,000 sympathies from the rainstorm
暴風雨で12万人のお見舞い
It can also be seen from here
ここからも見れます
High number of thefts
盗難件数が多い
is one thing we should not ignore
無視すべきではないことの一つです
Because there are too many of them
あまりにも多すぎるので、
Here I also mentioned the eight-line file
ここで 8 行のファイルについても触れました
The eighth line is now Chongqing
8号線は現在重慶です
Because of the emergence of eight-line files and
8 行ファイルの出現により、
so that we can study well
私たちがよく勉強できるように
these theft cases
こういった盗難事件は
good
良い
So let's introduce
それでは紹介しましょう
If the law of the Qing Dynasty
清朝の法なら
How to judge the so-called
いわゆるを判断する方法
regulate this law
この法律を規制する
How to regulate the problem of theft
盗難問題をどう規制するか
we know qing dynasty
私たちは清朝を知っています
General Laws of the Qing Dynasty
清朝の一般法
into two categories
2つのカテゴリーに分けて
one is green one is green
1 つは緑です 1 つは緑です
is a female Dharma
女ダルマです
In this law, in the crime of the sword
この法律では、刀の罪では
A few more important points
さらにいくつかの重要なポイント
First of all, it does not emphasize hand bugs
まず、手の虫を強調していない
That is, who is leading and who is following
つまり、誰が先頭に立って誰が従うのか
So the big brother who takes the lead is punished more severely.
したがって、先頭に立った兄はより厳しい罰を受けます。
The little brother I follow is a little lighter
追いかける弟は少し軽い
Second, he will pay attention to the problem of offenders and repeat offenders
第二に、犯罪者と再犯者の問題に注意を払うだろう。
That is to say, your autumn cut
つまり、あなたのオータムカット
If you committed a crime
犯罪を犯した場合
I will give you a lighter punishment
軽い罰を与えます
But when you get to the third offense
しかし、3回目の攻撃に到達すると、
That's behind the toes
それはつま先の後ろです
It's the highest law
それは最高の法律です
But it looks like everyone has two chances
でも誰にでもチャンスは2回あるようだ
that you can do it again
もう一度できるということ
The third important principle is called Ji Zhang Lun Punishment
3 番目の重要な原則は、季張倫罰と呼ばれます。
That is to say, for the Qing Dynasty, the theft
つまり、清朝にとっては窃盗である。
Its sentence is based on the value of the items you stole
その判決はあなたが盗んだ品物の価値に基づいて決まります
The higher the value, the higher your judgment
値が大きいほど判断力が高くなります
Walk
歩く
For example, like here, below one or two, it is judged as 60
例えばここのように、1～2以下だと60と判定されます。
This spanking only costs 60
このスパンキングの費用はたったの 60
But if you are 42 to 50 taels
ただし、42～50テールの場合
In addition to playing version 68, you
バージョン 68 をプレイすることに加えて、
You have another year in prison
あと一年の懲役だ
going to prison for one year
1年間刑務所に行くことになる
a year in prison
懲役一年
If you are 82 to 90 taels
82～90テールの場合
You don't need to fight 100
100回も戦う必要はない
you will be in prison for three years
あなたは3年間刑務所に入るでしょう
If it is 92 to 100 taels
92～100テールの場合
you still have to stay
あなたはまだ滞在しなければなりません
Except battle 100
バトル100を除く
you want to be popular
人気者になりたいですか
to distribute frontier
フロンティアを分配するには
To reserve two thousand miles
2,000マイルを予約するには
So wait until 120 taels or more
なので120テール以上になるまで待ちます
will pay the back
返済します
This sentence is based on the value of the amount you steal
この文はあなたが盗んだ金額に基づいています
I think the sentencing decider is very interesting
量刑決定は非常に興味深いと思う
If our current law
私たちの現在の法律であれば、
If such a sentence is used for a fraud case
このような文章が詐欺事件に使用された場合
most scammers
ほとんどの詐欺師
probably to death
おそらく死ぬほど
good
良い
Then in addition to the mother law
それから母法に加えて
law enforcement
法執行機関
There are also some changes
若干の変更点もあります
And the new crime situations they're adapting to
そして彼らが適応している新たな犯罪状況
Especially the tired meal is too much
特に疲れた食事は多すぎる
So everyone wants to define these tired meals
だから誰もがこの疲れた食事を定義したいのです
So give it a name called chicken foot slippery
だから、鶏の足滑りやすいという名前を付けてください
And find a way to prevent these tired meals from happening
そして、このような疲れた食事が起こらないようにする方法を見つけてください
So at that time, a kind of criminal law was invented in many places
それで当時、多くの場所で一種の刑法が発明されました。
It's called Iron Cover Iron Lock Strap
アイアンカバーアイアンロックストラップといいます
that is to say with a hardcore
つまりハードコアで
Then there must be an iron strap to lock it to the foot
それから足に固定するための鉄製のストラップが必要です
or locked in the neck
または首に閉じ込められている
Let it be carried like this
このまま運ばせて
avoid it later
後で避ける
do the theft again
また窃盗をする
But later we'll just look at an image and find out
でも後で画像を見て調べましょう
even though it already has this thing
たとえそれがすでにあるとしても
still commit crimes
まだ犯罪を犯している
In addition, it also mentioned that there is a principle
さらに、次の原則があることにも言及しました。
Just to increase the punishment
刑罰を重くするだけ
That is, there was violence during the theft.
つまり、盗難の際に暴力があったということです。
The crime of murder with a gray knife is aggravated
灰色のナイフによる殺人罪が加重される
Other crimes in certain places with special status
特定の場所で特別な地位を有するその他の犯罪
will also increase the penalty
罰金も増えるだろう
Those special status fields
特別なステータスフィールド
Status and place are usually related to the official or royal family
地位と地位は通常、役人または王室に関連しています
So if you committed a crime in a royal or official place
つまり、王室や公的な場所で犯罪を犯した場合、
you will pretend to be criminal
あなたは犯罪者のふりをするでしょう
There is another very interesting phenomenon
もう一つ非常に興味深い現象があります
But China's special situation
しかし、中国の特殊な状況
This is still the case in the Republic of China
中華民国では今でもそうだ
crimes against relatives
親族に対する犯罪
It is very special except criminal law
刑法以外は非常に特殊です
because of family crimes
家族の犯罪のせいで
it is based on your kinship to convict
有罪判決を受けるのはあなたの親族関係に基づく
So when you especially immediate family members
したがって、特に近親者がいるときは、
Its crimes, its convictions are very light
その罪も有罪判決も非常に軽い
not even guilty
罪さえない
Until now, in the Constitution of the Republic of China
これまで中華民国憲法では
sin of theft
窃盗の罪
If the son steals the books from the father's immediate family members
息子が父親の近親者から本を盗んだ場合
It's not a crime
それは犯罪ではありません
This is a very interesting penal code
とても興味深い刑法です
until now
今まで
In addition, of course, the type of dirt is also related to criminal responsibility.
また、汚れの種類によっても当然刑事責任が問われます。
That is, you stole the dirt
つまり、あなたは汚れを盗んだのです
If it is public dirt
公共垢であれば
It's official dirt
公式垢です
The penalty is even heavier
ペナルティはさらに重い
In addition, if you are involved in a crime
また、犯罪に巻き込まれた場合には、
In addition to the so-called master-slave
いわゆるマスタースレーブに加えて、
If you are a criminal harboring
あなたが犯罪者を匿っている場合
Or you are accepting his stamp
あるいは、あなたは彼のスタンプを受け入れています
there are penalties
罰則があります
In addition, the official duties must also be mature.
また、公務も成熟していなければなりません。
If you are an official or a patch
公式またはパッチの場合
none of you
あなた方の誰も
Didn't catch the thief
泥棒を捕まえられなかった
Even if he was not caught, there is a law to accept responsibility.
たとえ捕まらなかったとしても責任を負う法律はある。
Then obviously we can see the laws of the Qing Dynasty
そうすれば明らかに清朝の法律がわかります
He's not actually a piece of iron
彼は実際には鉄の塊ではありません
He will actually adapt to the changes in the whole society
彼は社会全体の変化に実際に適応するだろう
Also some new updates
いくつかの新しいアップデートもあります
And these laws and forces are constantly changing
そして、これらの法則と力は常に変化しています
so these criminals
それでこの犯罪者たちは
In the law of these congratulatory crimes
このおめでたい犯罪の法則では
In fact, the rules are quite detailed
実はルールがかなり細かいんです
Then use this method to congratulate the Lord for committing a crime
次に、この方法を使用して、犯罪を犯した主を祝福します。
Let's see next
次に見てみましょう
If a crime has occurred
犯罪が発生した場合
how does he report the crime
彼はどのように犯罪を報告しますか
how to deal with these
これらにどう対処するか
How does the government handle these processes
政府はこれらのプロセスをどのように処理しますか
when the crime first occurred
犯罪が最初に起こったとき
ordinary people
普通の人々
Maybe he didn't report to the police right away first.
おそらく彼はすぐに警察に通報しなかったのでしょう。
He first went to the neighborhood near his house
彼はまず家の近くに行きました
so-called group training
いわゆる集合研修
or Baojiachang
または宝家昌
He first talked with Tuan Lian and Bao Jia Chang
彼は最初にトゥアン・リアンとバオ・ジア・チャンと話しました。
He said so-and-so's house stole something from him
彼は、誰々の家族が彼から何かを盗んだと言いました
It's time for group training
グループ練習の時間です
With this Baojia chief, the two trillion
この宝家酋長とともに、二兆
to this place for mediation
調停のためこちらへ
Much like our mediation committee now
今の調停委員会によく似ています
Let's mediate first
まずは調停しましょう
If mediation fails
調停が不成立の場合
In the end they will sue
結局彼らは訴訟を起こすだろう
Then after suing the officer
その後警察官を告訴した後、
will present his son
彼の息子をプレゼントします
or pie
またはパイ
Say so and so or when in Zhuangzi
荘子にあれやこれやと言う。
my house was stolen
私の家が盗まれました
or when so and so stole from me
あるいは、あれやこれやが私から盗んだとき
what did you steal
何を盗んだのですか
I will list the so-called Shi Dan
いわゆる師団を挙げていきます
In Shidan, it will be listed as
Shidanでは、次のようにリストされます。
something was stolen from my house
私の家から何かが盗まれました
list them one by one
それらを一つずつ列挙していきます
even put his this
彼のこれを入れても
The price of this item will also be listed
この商品の価格も表示されます
then this time
それから今度は
After the branch accepts the report
支店が報告を受理した後
Then he started investigating
それから彼は調査を始めた
First of all, he will shoot calligraphy
まずは書道を撮影します
to that scene
あの場面へ
do something called this
これと呼ばれるものをやってください
CSI crime scene to do some investigation
CSI犯罪現場で捜査が行われる
An investigative report written after the crime scene investigation
犯罪現場の捜査後に作成される捜査報告書
call bulletin
電話連絡掲示板
This is the bulletin left at that time
これが当時残された会報です
This bulletin is written very carefully
この速報は非常に注意深く書かれています
They said this man, Yu Fuxing, had his home burglarized
この男性、Yu Fuxingは自宅に強盗に遭ったとのこと
where does he live
どこで住んていますか
He lives at the Jiaochangkou of the official temple
彼は官廟の焦昌口に住んでいます。
His house is a pavement
彼の家は舗道です
is a shop
店です
The distance between pavements is two
歩道間の距離は2です
There is a cabinet room in front
正面にキャビネットルームがあります
in front of the counter
カウンターの前で
There is a tall building in the back
奥に高い建物があります
Then there is a small door on the left side of the wall with a
次に、壁の左側に小さなドアがあります。
what's next near the middle
真ん中付近の次は何ですか
He also said that there was a piece of bamboo on his wall
彼はまた、壁に竹があったとも言いました。
but he is renovating
しかし彼は改装中です
So when he is on the street next to the outside
それで彼が外の隣の通りにいるとき
The walls of the refurbished bamboo pieces have no cement on the lake
改修された竹片の壁には湖にセメントがありません
So he said there were thieves at that time
それで彼はその時泥棒がいたと言った
the empty house next door to him
彼の隣の空き家
ran from his empty house to his house
空き家から彼の家まで走った
and then stole something
そして何かを盗んだ
He said the last book meaning, I found out from the investigation
彼は最後の本の意味を言った、私は調査で知った
This crossing is indeed a crossing.
この交差点は確かに交差点です。
How much does it measure? 20 1 inches wide and 1 15 inches wide
大きさはどれくらいですか? 幅1インチが20個、幅15インチが1個です。
Such this wall was found with damaged heart muscle
このような壁は心筋の損傷で発見されました
So he will do a survey like this
そこで彼はこのような調査を行う予定です
What about sometimes, the Shuyi Association said in a survey
時にはどうでしょうか、Shuyi Association が調査で答えました。
They found the scene, with the informant
彼らは情報提供者とともに現場を発見した
Reporter's description must not match
記者の説明は一致してはなりません
Then the branch will start to suspect that this may be a case of false reporting.
そうなると支店はこれは虚偽報告ではないかと疑い始める。
there will be such a judgment
そういう判断もあるだろう
Well, if it is determined that he is indeed a case,
まあ、彼が本当に事件であると判断された場合、
Calligraphy will start, and this branch line will send an official document to guess the ticket
書道が始まり、この支線がチケットを当てるための公式文書を送ります
Ask that man to start to mend, and then start to catch the bandit according to the plan
その男に修理を始めてもらい、それから計画に従って盗賊を捕まえ始めます
catch the thief
泥棒を捕まえます
Then if this supplement catches the thief
このサプリメントが泥棒を捕まえたら
he'll subpoena the victim
彼は被害者を召喚するだろう
and general
そして一般的な
A dry line of witnesses begins the interrogation
無表情の証人による尋問が始まる
Then the official document of these summons is called Peteran
そして、これらの召喚状の公式文書はPeteranと呼ばれます
Then after the arraignment they said
そして、罪状認否後、彼らはこう言いました。
Each will have their own job status and confession
それぞれが独自の職業と告白を持っています
how was that day
その日はどうでしたか
why am i
私はなぜ？
These final confessions are left behind and are called work certificates.
これらの最後の自白は残され、就労証明書と呼ばれます。
In the end, of course, the case was closed.
もちろん最終的には事件は解決しました。
we used to watch this tv
私たちはこのテレビを見ていました
there will be pressure
プレッシャーがかかるだろう
The pressure of the painting is a knot
絵の圧力は結び目です
The whole process looks like this
全体のプロセスは次のようになります
But in fact we will find
しかし実際には、私たちは見つけるでしょう
Most of the cases are basically unsolved
ほとんどの事件は基本的に未解決です
because most of the theft cases
盗難事件がほとんどだから
Very low detection rate
検出率が非常に低い
so let's see
それでは見てみましょう
now probably theft
今ではおそらく盗難
For example, in Taipei now
例えば今の台北では
In terms of the police capacity of Taipei City
台北市の警察能力について
Theft cases probably have a detection rate of 80 or 90%.
盗難事件の発見率はおそらく 80 ～ 90% です。
80, 90% or more
80、90%以上
Plus this monitor that we have installed for the last time
さらに、最後に設置したこのモニター
So in fact, the detection rate of this kind of theft is quite high.
したがって、実際、この種の盗難の検出率は非常に高いのです。
But in traditional things, it's actually not too high
しかし、伝統的なものでは実際にはそれほど高くはありません
There was a missionary
宣教師がいました
called Morrison
モリソンと呼ばれる
he had been to 1894
彼は1894年に行っていた
have been to chongqing
重慶に行ってきました
But he spoke highly of the public security in Chongqing.
しかし、彼は重慶の治安を高く評価した。
He said that the law and order in Chongqing is very good.
同氏は、重慶の法と秩序は非常に良好だと述べた。
very good
とても良い
But everyone should pay attention
でもみんなも気をつけたほうがいいよ
This description is actually a comparison
この説明は実際には比較です
are compared
比較される
In other words, when these Westerners came to China
言い換えれば、これらの西洋人が中国に来たとき、
He said good is not absolutely good
彼は良いことが絶対的に良いわけではないと言いました
is relatively good
比較的良いです
It was also compared to when he was in some cities in Europe
彼がヨーロッパのいくつかの都市にいたときとも比較されました
In China, Chongqing is a city with good law and order
中国の重慶は法と秩序が整った都市です
what is it actually like
実際はどうですか
uncertain
不確かな
Let's follow my statistics
私の統計に従ってみましょう
We see cases in the city
市内でも事例を見かけます
What happened in Chongqing at that time
その時重慶で何が起こったのか
There are more than 1,000 cases in the city
市内の感染者は1000人以上
Then
それから
In the end, only 204 suspects were obtained
最終的に得られた容疑者はわずか204人だった
So he only has a 19% cracking rate.
つまり、彼のクラッキング率はわずか 19% です。
country?
国？
His case count is more than 1900
彼の事件数は1900件以上
Getting a case to crack is 6
ケースをクラックするのは6です
The true detection rate is 33%.
真の検出率は 33% です。
In the countryside is better than in the city
都会より田舎のほうがいいよ
higher detection rate
より高い検出率
but even so
しかしそれでも
Its average detection rate is only 28%.
平均検出率はわずか 28% です。
So you can say this
だからこう言えます
Is the detection rate high?
検出率は高いのでしょうか？
of course not
もちろん違います
so it's only relatively good
だからそれは比較的良いだけです
relatively good
比較的良い
there is another interesting thing
もう一つ興味深いことがあります
is actually
実は
After many of these suspects were caught,
これらの容疑者の多くが逮捕された後、
put in jail
刑務所に入れられる
Most closed for less than a month
ほとんどが1か月以内に閉店
probably hang up
おそらく電話を切る
will die in prison
刑務所で死ぬだろう
Then you know that in this prison at that time
そうすれば、あの時この刑務所にいたことはわかるでしょう
In fact, the conditions are very bad
実は条件がかなり悪いんです
So a lot of these suspects are in jail
つまり、これらの容疑者の多くは刑務所にいます
It's hard to survive more than a month
1ヶ月以上生き続けるのは難しい
ok, let's see
わかりました、見てみましょう
Context affecting crime rates
犯罪率に影響を与える背景
I use this picture to estimate
この写真を使って推定します
During the gay boom
ゲイブームの頃
This cuts to the number of crimes
これで犯罪数が減る
everyone see
誰もが見る
From the first year of being gay to the 13th year of being gay
ゲイ歴1年目からゲイ歴13年目まで
its this cut to case number
これは事件番号に相当します
Very interesting
とても興味深い
There is an interesting phenomenon in this figure
この図には興味深い現象があります
That is to say
つまり
Comrades from the first year to the sixth year
1年生から6年生までの仲間たち
His theft cases are very high
彼の盗難事件は非常に多い
But after seven years of gay
しかし、7年間のゲイ生活を経て、
slowly lowered
ゆっくりと下げた
lowered a lot
かなり下げた
then this time
それから今度は
why during this time
なぜこの時期に
why is his case high
なぜ彼のケースが高いのか
In fact, if we take a closer look
実際、よく見てみると
In the historical background of the time
当時の歴史的背景の中で
You will find at least a few reasons
少なくともいくつかの理由が見つかるでしょう
is responsible for the growth of this cutter case
このカッターケースの成長を担っているのは
and also directly reflected in the
また、
Inside the case of the cutter case
カッターケースのケース内部
For example, the Taiping Heavenly Kingdom
例えば、太平天国
Everyone knows the Taiping Heavenly Kingdom
誰もが知っている太平天国
In fact, the first year of comrades is already the end of the strong humiliation
実際、同志の1年目はすでに強い屈辱の終わりです
But there was their
しかし、そこには彼らがいた
To Wing King Ten Open
要翼王十大開
He entered Chongqing in the first year of comrades
彼は同志の最初の年に重慶に入った
into Sichuan Province
四川省へ
harassed the harassed
嫌がらせをした
He entered Sichuan Province from here
ここから四川省に入った
Then he went to Guizhou
それから彼は貴州に行きました
Then in the second year of comrades
そして仲間の2年目で
He's here again from
彼はまたここから来ました
Arrived in Sichuan again
再び四川省に到着
Finally annihilated in this place
ついにこの場所で全滅した
But in the process of his arrival in Sichuan
しかし四川に到着する途中で
No direct access to Chongqing
重慶への直接アクセスはありません
But I have entered the surrounding areas of Chongqing
重慶市周辺に入ってきましたが
That is, around Baxin
つまりバシンのあたり
So at that time many cases
ですから当時は多くのケースが
cut into the case
ケースに切り込みます
It is said that many victims are group trainers
被害者の多くはグループトレーナーだという
Why did team training suffer?
なぜチームトレーニングがうまくいかなかったのでしょうか？
Because of the group practice, he has to go to many arts outlets
グループ練習のため、彼は多くの芸術店に行かなければなりません
to guard against these Taipings
これらの太平天国を防ぐために
But there is no one in his family
しかし彼の家族には誰もいない
So the house becomes
それで家はこうなります
Good example of a break-in
侵入の良い例
So a lot of team practice to defend Yikou
チームはイーコウを守るためにたくさんの練習をしました
When he came back, he found that his house had been burglarized.
戻ってきたら、家が強盗に遭っていたことが分かりました。
a lot of it is because
その多くは次のような理由からです
many of these victims
これらの犠牲者の多くは
It's because of the Taiping Heavenly Kingdom
太平天国のせいだよ
indirect damage
間接的な損害
What does the second reason have to do with it?
2番目の理由はそれと何の関係があるのでしょうか？
Happened with comrades for two years
2年間の仲間との出来事
The lesson plans in Chongqing are related
重慶の授業計画は関連しています
The Comrade Two Years Happened in Chongqing
重慶で起きた2年間の同志
Anti-Catholic Teaching Plan
反カトリック教育計画
At that time, many groups of mobs
その時、多くの暴徒のグループが
Just run to Catholics
カトリック教徒のところに走ってください
These residential areas go down
これらの住宅地は衰退する
to rob, to burn
盗む、燃やす
There are also many people taking advantage of this time
この時期を利用される方もたくさんいらっしゃいます
to name the thing that was stolen from that residence
その住居から盗まれた物の名前を言います
After those people who stole were slowly caught
盗んだ人々がゆっくりと捕まった後、
they tell their reasons
彼らは自分たちの理由を語る
It was when I was gay for two years
それは私が2年間同性愛者だったときのことです
I'm taking advantage of the chaos
混乱を利用している
Seeing this, I just touched something and came back
これ見て何か触って戻ってきた
So in fact this turmoil
それで実際、この混乱は
Endemic unrest can also affect cheetao cases
風土病の不安はチタオの症例にも影響を与える可能性がある
Then the third reason is related to the price
3つ目の理由は価格に関するものです
related to this economic change
この経済変化に関連した
Because in the three years of many comrades
多くの同志は3年だから
a lot of these thieves got caught
これらの泥棒の多くが捕まりました
His statement said
彼の声明はこう言った
Why did I steal that year
なぜあの年に私は盗んだのか
Because he said that the price of rice was too expensive that year
その年は米の値段が高す​​ぎたと言っていたから
It's too high for me to live
私が住むには高すぎる
so now i have to steal
だから今私は盗まなければならない
Is it like this let's see
こんな感じですか、見てみましょう
Actually this is what I got from
実はこれは私がもらったものなんです
inside the file
ファイルの中に
a price list
価格表
We will find that in 1864 when
1864 年にそれがわかります。
The price of rice has suddenly risen
米の値段が急に上がった
and increased several times
そして数倍に増えた
The highest rice price is from 2 taels
米の最高価格は2俵から
Rise to 3.5 Taels
3.5 テールに上昇
It's going to be high
高くなるよ
The same is true for the lowest rice price
米の最低価格も同様
So in the third year of Tongzhi
それで同治三年に
Because of the sudden rise in the price of rice
米価の高騰により
At that time, there were many people because of the high price of rice
当時は米が高かったので人が多かった
he ended up having trouble living
彼は結局生きるのに苦労することになった
end up stealing
結局盗むことになる
The fourth reason is a long-term factor
4 番目の理由は長期的な要因です
Long-term factors have a lot to do with urbanization
長期的な要因は都市化と大きく関係している
Why? This is a statistic I made
なぜですか? これは私が作った統計です
The urban population of this eighth-tier region
この 8 層地域の都市人口
This is his total population
これは彼の総人口です
Let's figure out the percentage of urbanization in his city
彼の都市の都市化の割合を計算してみましょう
As you can see in 1824
ご覧のとおり、1824年に
The proportion of urbanization is 14%
都市化率は14%
This is probably the traditional Chinese period
これはおそらく伝統的な中国の時代です
average proportion of urbanization in general
一般的な都市化の平均割合
about ten percent
約10パーセント
But by the 1860s
しかし1860年代までに
That's when it's good to have the same government
そういう時は同じ政府が良いんだよ
His urbanization ratio suddenly rose to 32%
彼の都市化率は突然 32% に上昇しました
this city
この街
Chongqing city developed in private land
私有地を開発した重慶市
He changed from a population of tens of thousands
彼は数万人の人口から変わった
Population from 65,000 to 200,000
人口65,000人から200,000人へ
The degree of urbanization suddenly increased at this time
この頃から都市化の度合いが一気に高まった
Then continue to grow slowly and continuously
その後もゆっくりと継続的に成長し続けます
So at this time we will find
したがって、現時点では次のようになります。
If we compare the 18th century to the mid-19th century
18世紀と19世紀半ばを比較すると
You can find an interesting phenomenon
面白い現象が見つかるかも
In the second half of the 18th century during the Qianlong Dynasty
18世紀後半、乾隆王朝の時代
His theft case is actually not too many
彼の盗難事件は実はそれほど多くない
Only more than 300 pieces
300個以上のみ
Then the proportion that happens in the city is 19%
すると都市部で起こる割合は19%
Occurred in rural areas is 81%
農村部で発生する割合は 81%
So most of the cases are in rural areas
したがって、ほとんどのケースは田舎にあります
But in Tong Zhichao's 3,000-plus theft cases,
しかし、Tong Zhichao の 3,000 件以上の盗難事件では、
The proportion of cities takes place in cities as high as 33%
都市で行われる割合は33%にも上る
The proportion that occurred in rural areas has dropped to 59%
農村部で発生した割合は59%に低下
So this whole trend is related to urbanization
つまり、この傾向全体が都市化に関連しているということです
So urbanization will actually affect the growth of the crime rate
つまり都市化は実際に犯罪率の増加に影響を与える
Especially in the urban crime growth
特に都市部の犯罪の増加においては
this is a situation
これは状況です
Okay, the next question is fun.
さて、次の質問は楽しいですね。
What kind of person is likely to become a thief
泥棒になりやすいのはどんな人ですか
What kind of person is prone to crime
どのような人が犯罪に遭いやすいのか
Generally we think that
一般的に私たちはこう考えています
Especially the so-called fringe people who don't do their jobs properly
特に、自分の仕事を適切に行わない、いわゆるフリンジの人々
a so-called dangerous class
いわゆる危険クラス
Including things like implement, beggar
実装、乞食などを含む
No business, or some thieves
用事がないか、泥棒がいる
Hooligans, liars
フーリガン、嘘つき
OK, but I'm based on myself from this cutter case
OK、でも私はこのカッターケースからの自分をベースにしています
Tong Zhichao's case made some statistics
董志超氏の事件はいくつかの統計をとった
The number of these people is certainly not small.
こうした人々の数は決して少なくありません。
But the real, the real majority is this group of people
しかし、本当の、本当の多数派はこのグループの人々です
Xia Li is alive
シア・リーは生きている
they are working class
彼らは労働者階級です
But the fluid working class
しかし流動的な労働者階級
He is not the same as the sailor on the ship and the porter
彼は船の船員やポーターとは同じではありません
Because sailors and porters are regular occupations
船員やポーターは本職だから
they have trade unions
彼らには労働組合がある
they have fixed groups
彼らには固定されたグループがある
But this Xia Li is not a fixed industry group
しかし、このXia Liは固定された業界グループではありません
So this group of people is the group of people who are most prone to stealing.
したがって、このグループの人々は、最も盗みをする傾向にある人々のグループです。
steal a bunch of people
大勢の人を盗む
but except for these people
でも、この人たちを除いて
Except in more than 200 months
200か月を超える場合を除く
More than 200 Summer Law live outside
屋外には 200 人以上のサマー ローが住んでいます
everyone can see
誰もが見ることができます
There are so many businessmen
ビジネスマンもたくさんいるよ
There are more than 100 people employed in the service industry
サービス業では100人以上が働いている
civil servant or gene
公務員か遺伝子か
He himself may be a thief
彼自身が泥棒かもしれない
We have some social relations
私たちはある程度の社会的関係を持っています
so this lets us
これで、
thought of another interesting thing
他に面白いことを思いついた
would be a thief
泥棒だろう
Not necessarily all directly related to poverty
必ずしもすべてが貧困に直接関係しているわけではない
Because some people are professional
プロの人もいるから
also have income
収入もある
but they steal
しかし彼らは盗みます
so what's the reason
それで、理由は何ですか
Next we discuss
次に議論します
question of motive
動機の問題
The question of motive for theft
窃盗の動機の問題
Do the poor always steal?
貧乏人はいつも盗みをするのでしょうか？
that's right
それは正しい
they may be inclined to steal
彼らは盗む傾向があるかもしれない
but not all
すべてではありません
poor people steal
貧しい人々は盗みをする
And why the poor steal
そしてなぜ貧しい人は盗むのか
there are many promotions
多くのプロモーションがあります
the reason it becomes a thief
泥棒になる理由
and motivation
和動機
Next we start with
次に始めます
From the vantage point
見晴らしの良い場所から
especially through
特にそれを通して
The mouths of these criminals in the file
ファイルにあるこれらの犯罪者の口
Everyone states that they are so-called criminals
誰もが自分たちはいわゆる犯罪者だと言います
look at his criminal motives
彼の犯行動機を見てください
Then we will put some theories of this criminology
次に、この犯罪学の理論をいくつか紹介します。
time to analyze the motives of these crimes
これらの犯罪の動機を分析する時が来た
you'll discover the theory of criminology
あなたは犯罪学の理論を発見するでしょう
very effective in explaining the causes of crime in history
歴史における犯罪の原因を説明するのに非常に効果的です
First of all, there is a bias in criminology
まず第一に、犯罪学には偏見がある
rational choice theory
合理的な選択理論
That is to say, when ordinary people commit crimes
つまり、一般人が犯罪を犯すと、
feel like I'm stealing
盗んでいるような気がする
The result will be better than my
結果は私よりも良くなるでしょう
Now my situation is much better
今、私の状況はずっと良くなりました
I choose to steal
私は盗むことを選びます
This situation is used to explain
この状況は説明するために使用されます
Like Xia Li, a living poor person
シア・リーのように貧しい暮らしをしている人
Why would they choose to steal
なぜ彼らは盗むことを選ぶのでしょうか
That's because they judged that the times they lived in were not good
それは彼らが生きてきた時代が良くないと判断したからだ
if we steal
私たちが盗むなら
can make my life a little better
私の人生を少し良くすることができます
This is called rational choice theory
これを合理的選択理論といいます
But then there is another problem
しかし、その後、別の問題が発生します
We will find a very interesting situation
非常に興味深い状況が見つかります
when many poor people are stealing
多くの貧しい人々が盗みをしているとき
he didn't steal alone
彼は一人で盗んだわけではない
he is a group host
彼はグループのホストです
Kind of like a crime syndicate stealing
犯罪組織の窃盗みたいなもんだな
this is fun
これは楽しいです
we actually see a lot
私たちは実際にたくさん見ています
Confessions stolen by eighth-line party members
8線党員が自白を盗む
Director Zhang San Wang Ermazi
監督 チャン・サン・ワン・エルマジ
they are poor
彼らは貧しい
One day in the ruined temple
ある日、廃墟となった神殿で
suddenly everyone gathers together
突然みんなが集まる
Discuss that everyone's life is so sad
みんなの人生がとても悲しいことについて話し合う
Why don't we work together
一緒に働きませんか
to steal
盗む
And they'll all have a plan to steal
そして彼らは皆、盗む計画を持っているでしょう
Which family has silver at home?
家に銀があるのはどの家庭ですか?
So this according to social psychology
つまり、社会心理学によれば、
social aggregation theory
社会的集合理論
That is to say
つまり
when people are single
人が独身のとき
your criminal
あなたの犯罪者
not so bold
それほど大胆ではない
But when you become a group of people
しかし、人々のグループになると、
you are getting bolder
あなたは大胆になっています
courage is getting bigger and bigger
勇気はどんどん大きくなる
social aggregation theory
社会的集合理論
The third one we talked about
3番目に話したのは
except the poor steal
貧しい盗みを除いて
some people are poor
貧しい人もいる
some people have careers
キャリアのある人もいる
but why would he steal
しかしなぜ彼は盗むのでしょうか
is related to the third
3番目に関係します
the theory of criminology
犯罪学の理論
everyday life theory
日常生活理論
This theory of everyday life which states that
こう述べる日常生活理論。
especially theft
特に盗難
Continue to have three elements
3つの要素を持ち続ける
The first element, of course, is
最初の要素はもちろん、
criminally inclined thief
犯罪傾向のある泥棒
the second
二番目
you must have a goal
あなたには目標があるはずです
valuable stolen item
貴重な盗品
the subject matter
主題
The third element is to have
3 番目の要素は、
In the absence of supervisors
監督者不在の場合
That is to say, the combination of these three reasons
つまり、この3つの理由が組み合わさって、
crime will happen
犯罪が起こるだろう
you have criminal tendencies today
あなたは今日犯罪傾向があります
you saw a valuable phone
貴重な電話を見ました
Then there was no one around
そしたら周りに誰もいなくなった
no one nor monitor
誰もいないし監視者もいない
next thing you want to say
次に言いたいこと
This is a gift from God
これは神様からの贈り物です
take it now
今すぐ受け取ってください
let me steal
盗ませてください
So this so-called opportunism
つまり、このいわゆるご都合主義
the theory of everyday life
日常生活の理論
So we actually often see
実際に私たちがよく目にするのは、
a lot of thieves are like this
泥棒ってこういう人が多いよ
special we iron tail says
特別な私たちアイアンテールは言います
will mention cattle stealing
牛の窃盗について言及するでしょう
Many people because of rural people
田舎者なので人が多い
After grazing the cattle, they put them in the countryside
彼らは放牧した牛を田舎に放牧した
sometimes there are people
時々人がいる
it ain't no work
それは仕事じゃない
it ain't without a job
仕事がないわけではない
it's not without income
収入がないわけではない
But when it passed the paddy field
しかし田んぼを過ぎると
see the cow over there
あそこの牛を見てください
no more manpower
もう人手はいない
And at this time feel
そしてこの時の気持ちは
Just let me take the bull by the hand
雄牛の手を取らせてください
just took it away
それを奪っただけです
In fact, there are many such cases
実際にそのようなケースは多々あります
There are many cases of this
このようなケースはたくさんあります
I just saw it walking in the shops in this city
この街の店を歩いているのを見たところだ
Found the shop door open
お店のドアが開いているのを見つけた
in stock
在庫あり
but no one is watching
でも誰も見てない
It goes in and steals
それは侵入して盗みます
So the situation is
したがって、状況は次のとおりです
This can explain the third
これで 3 つ目の理由が説明できます
But the fourth one is fun
でも4つ目も面白いよ
I want to explain
説明したいのですが
The fourth is to use this criminological theory
4 番目は、この犯罪理論を使用することです。
Called Situational Prevention Traveler Inside
内部の状況防止トラベラーと呼ばれる
He mentioned that many criminals
彼は犯罪者が多いと述べた
He is in a situation
彼はある状況にある
in everyday situations
日常の場面で
Some are criminal motives
犯罪動機もある
especially if they are likely to be related by blood
特に血がつながっている可能性が高い場合
with geographical or business relationship
地理的またはビジネス上の関係
as long as under the circumstances
状況下である限り
a little chance
ちょっとしたチャンス
is likely to encourage it to steal
盗むことを奨励する可能性が高い
In terms of blood relationship
血のつながりという意味では
The most common is that the son steals the father's money
最も一般的なのは、息子が父親のお金を盗むことです
Geographical relations are neighbors
地理的関係は隣人です
Stealing a neighbor's money
隣人のお金を盗む
employee relations is
従業員関係は
Hired worker stealing from boss
雇われた労働者が上司から盗む
This is a situation caused by a situation
これは状況によって引き起こされた状況です
so this i say
だから私はこう言います
Why
なぜ
Spit gun is not necessarily
スピットガンは必ずしも必要ではありません
No money
お金がない
Maybe he has a business
もしかしたら彼には用事があるのか​​もしれない
rich income
豊かな収入
But it's possible to commit a crime
でも犯罪を犯す可能性もある
that is
あれは
this little house
この小さな家
At that time, this stupid thief stole the root
その時、この愚かな泥棒が根を盗んだ
Because he sees if anyone is watching
なぜなら彼は誰かが見ているかどうかを確認しているからです
He secretly went to the city to sell
彼は密かに街へ売りに行った
I probably know that the reason is so big once
理由がとても大きいことは一度は知っているかもしれない
Calibration is so large
キャリブレーションが非常に大きい
So many people said
とても多くの人が言いました
would rather steal a sheep
むしろ羊を盗むだろう
don't steal a sheep
羊を盗まないでください
Next we look at this
次にこれを見ます
Types of crime and the process of crime
犯罪の種類と犯罪の過程
Generally we
一般的に私たちは
we say
私達は言う
like a beautiful one
美しいもののように
Bird tree for the enjoyment of skills
技を楽しむ鳥の木
we might think
私たちは考えるかもしれない
Wang Yi said
王毅は言った
This kind of nonsense
この種のナンセンス
pro-communist is very good
親共産主義者はとても良い
this non
この非
is crime the norm
犯罪は常態ですか
so many crimes
とても多くの犯罪
will be higher
より高くなります
After these were stolen
これらが盗まれた後
Are they avenues with or without disassembly
解体の有無に関わらず、
And are there some black hands behind them?
そして、彼らの後ろに黒い手がいますか？
Well in fact
まあ実際のところ
We actually see
私たちは実際に見ています
Most of these fly the above
これらのほとんどは上記を飛行します
In fact, not everyone knows
実は誰もが知っているわけではない
It's not that hard to clean up
掃除するのはそれほど難しくありません
everyone practiced
みんなが練習した
Not every kid has a cleaner
すべての子供が掃除機を持っているわけではありません
then most often as a form of stealing
それから最も頻繁に盗みの一形態として
is the so-called road pattern
いわゆる道路パターンです
And the most commonly used way to find the image is
画像を見つけるために最も一般的に使用される方法は、
move the walls away
壁を遠ざける
That's what we see in this painting
それがこの絵で私たちが見ているものです
just inside the wall
壁のすぐ内側
this is the most common
これが最も一般的です
In addition, theft is also common
また、盗難も多発しています
There is another way we think
別の考え方もあります
only now
現在才有
In fact, there were gold plates in ancient times.
実際、古代には金のプレートがありました。
Just use our famous cigarettes
当社の有名なタバコを使用してください
That famous drug comes in the name of someone's theft
あの有名な麻薬は誰かの窃盗の名の下にある
In fact, this can only appear in the bottom line
実際、これは最後の行にのみ表示されます
Another thing is stealing
もう一つは盗むことです
It's the common practice of stealing things
物を盗むのはよくある行為だ
But the most common one is actually road image
しかし、実際に最も一般的なのは道路の画像です
next might be interesting
次は面白いかもしれない
Hot funds that can be stolen many times
何度でも盗まれる可能性のあるホットな資金
Usually it is the test base
通常はテストベースです
Exam period
試験期間
And when the market is open
そして市場が開いているときは
Another one is when the wedding is followed.
もう一つは結婚式が続いたときです
This situation is actually at the meeting room
この状況は実際に会議室で
Because many times the wedding photos are stolen
結婚式の写真は盗まれることが多いので
In addition, when these thieves are arrogant, how can they be arrogant?
さらに、これらの盗人が傲慢であるとき、どうして彼らは傲慢になることができますか？
Knots as part of more experienced thieves
より経験豊富な泥棒の一員としてのノット
They will analyze the things that steal drugs to be arrogant
彼らは麻薬を盗むものを傲慢に分析するでしょう
He won't be arrogant all the time
彼はいつも傲慢になるわけではない
Because he knows that the goal of being arrogant all the time is too low-level
常に傲慢でいることの目標があまりにも低レベルであることを彼は知っているからです
So where could he be arrogant?
それでは、どこで彼は傲慢になるのでしょうか？
He may go to the pawnshop to be a pawn
彼は質屋に行って質屋になるかもしれない
He may go to the market and set up a stall in those markets to sell directly
彼は市場に行き、直接販売するためにそれらの市場に屋台を設置するかもしれません
he may also sell directly to the checkout
レジに直接販売することもできます
said to take care of
世話すると言った
Then let's look at
それでは見てみましょう
Is there a so-called black hand behind the scenes?
いわゆる黒幕がいるのだろうか？
It was called my home in the post office at that time
当時郵便局は私の家と呼ばれていました
The explanation is called Wojia
説明はWojiaと呼ばれます
And these nests usually open inns
そしてこれらの巣は通常宿屋を開いています
open an inn
旅館を開く
So those officials feel
だから当局者たちはこう感じている
The best way to develop this nest
この巣を発展させる最良の方法
Even Baojia and the law
宝家と法律さえも
Use this method to lift up these innkeepers
この方法を使用して、これらの宿屋の主人を持ち上げてください
because of their
彼らのせいで
You see, the inn is also an inn
ほら、旅館も旅館ですよ
is big or small
大きいか小さいか
If you use the law to make an appointment with Baojia
法律を利用してBaojiaとの約束をした場合
The so-called opening an inn and becoming a home
いわゆる旅館を開業して自宅になること
This is an important crime prevention method
大切な防犯手段です
ok so next question
はい、それでは次の質問です
what kind of person is easy to be stolen
どんな人が盗まれやすいのか
Do you think rich people are easy to be stolen?
お金持ちは盗まれやすいと思いますか?
actually not
実際にはそうではありません
our current statistics
現在の統計
This is my statistic from the answer
これは回答から得た私の統計です
You can know
知ることができます
Most of the stolen ones were merchants
盗まれた者のほとんどは商人でした
In fact, generations of scientists
実際、何世代にもわたる科学者は、
and some workers
そして何人かの労働者
In fact, those who are really rich in this so-called co-existing drama
実際、このいわゆる共生ドラマの中で本当に裕福な人たちは、
In fact, it adds up to less votes
実際、合計すると得票数は減ります
So we say that most people will be voted
したがって、ほとんどの人が投票するだろうと言います
They're all so-called middle-class families.
いわゆる中流家庭です。
or Chinese House
またはチャイニーズハウス
So how many people are there in Chinese House and Chinese House?
それで、チャイニーズハウスとチャイニーズハウスには何人いますか？
According to the status at that time, there were probably more than 100 taels
当時の状況によると、テイルはおそらく100体以上いたと思われる
how much is it
いくらですか
Not more than 100 taels
テイルが100個以下
And then less than 1000 taels of such a moment
そして、そのような瞬間の1000テイル未満
so-called middle-class home
いわゆる中流家庭
Then if you have more than 1000 taels
テイルが1000以上ある場合
was recognized at that time
当時認められた
1000 taels are responsible
1000テールが担当
So let's look at the voted
それでは投票結果を見てみましょう
Probably Chinese House
おそらく中国人の家
In fact, when the democrats
実際、民主党が政権を握ったとき、
At that time, many people already realized that
その時すでに多くの人が気づいていましたが、
So many opinions say
という意見がとても多いです
When the bandits come
山賊が来ると
The most vulnerable is the so-called Chinese House
最も脆弱なのはいわゆる中国の家です
Then these Chinese homes
それから、これらの中国人の家は
Will they choose to report to the police?
彼らは警察に通報することを選択するでしょうか？
In fact, in traditional Chinese
実は繁体字中国語では
There are also many people who say that the reporter
記者はという人も多い。
become a black art
黒魔術になる
So the criminal's black art is in some
つまり、犯罪者の黒魔術は一部にあります
market appears
市場出現
And there are many
そしてたくさんあります
So these things I said today
今日私が言ったことは
Actually true is not really the number of possible
実際に真実は実際に可能な数ではありません
much higher than these
これらよりもはるかに高い
Then why did they report to the police?
ではなぜ彼らは警察に通報したのでしょうか？
There are also several reasons
理由もいくつかあります
Sometimes because of the pulled
引っ張られたせいで時々
actually every time
実は毎回
we see actual cases
実際の事例を見ていきます
Every time it is pulled
引っ張られるたびに
The value of that thing is actually not that high
実はその物の価値はそこまで高くない
except for a few
一部を除いて
It will exceed dozens of taels of silver
銀の数十尾を超えるだろう
or this for up to a hundred people
またはこれは最大 100 人まで
Most of the silver
ほとんどが銀
Most of these silver taels that were pulled
引っ張られた銀の尾のほとんどは
They are actually only one tael or two taels of silver
実際には銀の 1 テールまたは 2 テールにすぎません。
Then for the middle class data
次に、中間層のデータについてです。
Actually such value
実際にそのような値
such this
こんなこと
such a price
そんな値段
or such a value
またはそのような値
It's actually not that big of a loss.
実際にはそれほど大きな損失ではありません。
So usually they may choose to report to the official
したがって、通常は当局に報告することを選択する可能性があります
depends on them
彼ら次第です
The reason for their customs declaration this time is because
今回の税関申告の理由は、
sometimes at the end of sleep
時々眠りの終わりに
winter time
冬時間
Because the government is at the end of his sleep
政府はもう眠りについたから
He does not accept reports
彼は報告を受け付けない
so even if it happens
だからたとえそれが起こったとしても
You went to report the crime and he didn't accept it.
あなたは犯罪を通報しに行きましたが、彼はそれを受け入れませんでした。
So sometimes many cases
だから時々多くの場合
In fact, at the end of sleep
実は眠りの終わりに
He actually became a criminal melanin
彼は実際に犯罪者メラニンになった
Another possibility is
もう一つの可能​​性は、
in the process of reporting
報告の過程で
many victims he felt
彼が感じた多くの犠牲者
his risk is higher
彼のリスクはより高い
because no matter from the countryside
田舎だから関係なく
or to the city's platform
または市のプラットフォームへ
in the countryside
田舎で
sometimes you take a long time
時には長い時間がかかることもあります
get the door now
今すぐドアを手に入れてください
In the middle, there are actually considerable risks
真ん中には実はかなりのリスクがある
And it costs a lot
そして、かなりの費用がかかります
Not necessarily after customs declaration
必ずしも税関申告後ではない
you can really get it back
本当に取り戻せるよ
with the original header item
元のヘッダー項目を使用して
Therefore, many people think that it is not a declaration
そのため、宣言ではないと考える人も多いでしょう。
This is the cause of many criminal melanin administration
これが多くの犯罪的メラニン投与の原因です
Plus everyone knows
それに加えて誰もが知っている
I also analyzed earlier
私も以前分析しました
Only a 28% detection rate
検出率はわずか 28%
think about it
考えてみてください
You are the master of ten, so your case has been dragged by this extreme tree
あなたは10のマスターなので、あなたのケースはこの極端な木に引きずられています
Then your family lives far away from Xinshan, Xinshan
そうすると、あなたの家族は遠く離れた新山市に住んでいます。
Think about it, forget it, the reporting officer may not have actually done a case
考えてみてください、忘れてください、報告担当官は実際に事件を担当していない可能性があります
So most of them will probably choose the reporting officer
したがって、彼らのほとんどはおそらく報告担当者を選択するでしょう
what are we going to see next
次は何を見ますか
Thieves love to drag
泥棒は引きずるのが大好き
A few days ago I was talking to an Israeli friend about this time
数日前、私はイスラエル人の友人とこの時のことについて話していました
I guessed with him, saying that he is doing Buddhism
私は彼と一緒に、彼は仏教をやっていると言いました。
I said you guess
私はあなたが推測すると言いました
what is most often dragged
最も頻繁に引きずられるもの
And the jewelry, right?
そして宝石ですよね？
I said no
私はノーと言った
I said cows, I said cows, there are many cows, but not the most
牛って言った、牛って言った、牛はたくさんいるけど、一番多いわけではない
but he said what is it
でも彼は、それは何だと言った
I said that the person who is most often dragged is
一番引きずられるのは、と言いました。
clothes, clothes are the most often dragged
衣服、衣服が最も頻繁に引きずられます
Then this clothes being dragged is not a Chinese characteristic
となると、この服を引きずっているのは中国人の特徴ではない
It's the same in Europe
ヨーロッパでも同じです
Clothes were the most frequently dragged in Britain and France in early modern Europe
近世ヨーロッパのイギリスとフランスで最も頻繁に引きずられたのは衣類であった
so why are the clothes dragged
ではなぜ服が引きずられるのか
The most common passive is actually related to consumption
最も一般的なパッシブは実際には消費に関連しています
In fact, this East and West in the early modern
実はこの東洋と西洋、近世では
fashion of things
物事のファッション
especially consumer clothes
特に消費者の衣類
One more form of fashion
もう一つのファッションの形
So many people steal clothes and sell them better
服を盗んで高く売る人がたくさんいます
Because the most people want it
ほとんどの人がそれを望んでいるから
So why should we talk about a US-Taiwan
では、なぜ米国と台湾について話す必要があるのでしょうか。
Run to New York Road to steal clothes
服を盗むためにニューヨークロードまで走る
from a
から
That's because it's so good at cooking
それは料理が上手だからです
and very nice
そしてとても素敵です
Actually operating gas
実は、作動ガスは
like camp
キャンプのように
camp meals these snacks
キャンプの食事、こんなおやつ
very easy to burn
非常に燃えやすい
easy to steal
盗みやすい
In addition, daily necessities
その他、日用品
originally deep class
元々ディープクラス
Like cows, chickens, ducks and other deep species
牛、鶏、アヒル、その他の深層種のような
in the eighteenth century in the former east
18世紀に旧東部で
The ratio of being stolen is quite high.
盗まれる確率はかなり高いです。
But in the nineteenth century
しかし19世紀には
The proportions stolen from these depths of agriculture
農業の奥深くにあるこれらの割合が盗まれています
lower a lot
かなり下げる
because the reason is very simple
理由はとても簡単なので
because rich people
なぜなら金持ちの人は
people with money
お金を持っている人
Can not be regarded as concentrated in the city
都市に集中しているとは考えられない
So most thieves start asking for
そこで、ほとんどの泥棒は次のことを求め始めます。
if he chooses to spit
彼が唾を吐くことを選択した場合
He will choose something that is easier to carry and more valuable
彼は持ち運びが簡単で価値の高いものを選ぶでしょう
Most of those are in the city
そのほとんどが市内にある
Then I said just now that when I reported the crime
それから私は今言いました、犯罪を報告したとき
He'll make a poem list of what he's ripping
彼は自分が盗んだものの詩リストを作るだろう
This is one of the poetry lists at that time
これは当時の詩集の一つです
He'll say what he tore up for himself
彼は自分のために引き裂いたものを言うだろう
You still have to pretend that there are a lot of Chinese words written in the city
まだ街には中国語がたくさん書かれているふりをしなければなりません
And Xiaoyi
そしてシャオイー
and hat
そして帽子
In fact, sheep shops in the clothing category are the most frequently listed
実際、衣料品カテゴリーの羊ショップが最も頻繁にリストされています。
It's the most frequent thief on this cruise.
このクルーズで最も多い泥棒です。
There is also this horse maniac below
以下にこんな馬マニアもいます
and cloth
と布
These can't be seen
これらは見えません
There are also casual men
カジュアルなメンズもいますよ
So we can see here
ここでわかります
This is when these clothes
こういうときはこの服が
why everyday language is so good
なぜ日常言語は優れているのか
There are actually a lot of sheep shops in there.
実は羊のお店がたくさんあるんです。
For example, these sheep shops
たとえば、こちらの羊屋さん
The things on the shoulders are some sheep shop
肩に乗っているのは羊屋さん
You can see this sheep shop here
羊のお店はこちらからご覧いただけます
in the wild
野生で
In China, it is actually very immortal
中国では実際には非常に不死です
There's actually something in there
実はそこに何かがあるんです
i didn't list it
私はそれをリストしませんでした
especially some cultural goods
特に一部の文化品
cultural goods
文化商品
Don't talk about Yantai
煙台のことは話さないで
And very high-grade wood
そして非常に高級な木材です
and Shuhua
とシュファ
These things are actually found inside
これらは実際に内部にあります
But from inside we can see these cultural goods
しかし、内側からはこれらの文化財が見えます
is a drifter
漂流者です
It's the benefactor
恩人だよ
In fact, it doesn't have to be a senior official.
実際、それは高官である必要はない。
But it's definitely something called citizenship
でもそれは間違いなく市民権と呼ばれるものだ
So these cultural goods
ですから、これらの文化品は、
In fact, these people
実はこの人たち、
A symbolic way of wanting to follow its identity and taste
そのアイデンティティと味わいを守りたいという象徴的な方法
these problems are there
これらの問題はそこにあります
but which are the richest
しかし、誰が最も裕福ですか
stolen richest
盗まれた大金持ち
actually an official
実は公務員
Because for the top consumption
なぜならトップ消費のために
This tradition is really consuming top things
この伝統は本当に一流のものを消費しています
is advanced
先進的です
So we see a max coffee steal
つまり、最大のコーヒー盗みが見られます
It's actually a matter of design
実はデザインの問題なんです
ok , so let ' s take another look at the cities
さて、都市をもう一度見てみましょう
We're discussing the biggest relationship this crime firm has with the city.
私たちはこの犯罪会社と市との最大の関係について話し合っています。
It's about discussing which places are most prone to crime
どの場所が最も犯罪が発生しやすいかを話し合うことです
These so-called crime hotspots, crime problems
これらのいわゆる犯罪ホットスポット、犯罪問題
I have a friend who studies Shanghai
私には上海を研究している友人がいます
He studied Shanghai's Little Britain period through
彼は上海のリトルブリテン時代を研究しました。
He found that, crawling hands, the most common case of crawling hands
彼は、手を這うのが最も一般的なケースであることを発見しました。
all concentrated at the intersection of the road
すべてが道路の交差点に集中している
ok , that ' s a road cross
わかりました、それは道路の交差点です
Like running away after stealing something
何かを盗んで逃げるような
Because he has many routes to choose from
彼には選択できるルートがたくさんあるから
less easy to catch
捕まえるのが難しくなる
Let's take a look at this and see that the case happened in a traditional city.
これを見て、この事件が伝統的な都市で起こったことを見てみましょう。
What areas can everyone enter
誰でも入れるエリアは
Of course I didn't study as detailed as my friend
もちろん私は友達ほど詳しく勉強したわけではありません
Then I use this picture of Chongqing
それから重慶のこの写真を使います
This is the city map of Chongqing in the Qing Dynasty at that time
これは当時の清朝の重慶の市内地図です。
Then we update this to get Chongqing
次に、これを更新して重慶を取得します
At that time, his in various regions
当時、彼は各地で
access his function
彼の機能にアクセスする
like this block in blue
この青いブロックのように
is the business district
ビジネス街です
red block
赤いブロック
is the administrative area
行政区域です
like this block is the parish
このブロックが教区であるように
So we just had a little talk with God
そこで私たちは神と少しだけ話をしました
The place between these temples
これらの寺院の間の場所
this is the transport zone
ここは輸送ゾーンです
because there are many piers
桟橋がたくさんあるので
Then this is the so-called stone pipe
それからこれはいわゆる石管です
because later this
この後だから
After the opening of the five-port trade
五港貿易開設後
There are a lot of places between the stone pipes
石管の間にはたくさんの場所があります
then let's see
それでは見てみましょう
next picture
次の写真
This picture is to see this cut to the case
この写真はケースのカットを見るものです
Which spaces are the longest among them
その中で最も長いスペースはどれですか
we see the darkest
私たちは最も暗いものを見ます
more than fifty
50以上
Orthodox and Orthodox and Orthodox
正統派と正統派と正統派
But these two areas
しかし、この 2 つの領域
In fact, it is a business district and an administrative district.
実はここはビジネス街であり行政街でもあるのです。
So in traditional cities
つまり伝統的な都市では
Cut to the longest of the cases
ケースの最長部分にカット
Is in the business district and administrative district
ビジネス地区と行政地区にあります
this is the case
これは事実です
I think when going to the end
最後まで行くと思う
i want to discuss
議論したいです
In the Qing Dynasty, the way of cutting
清代の切断方法
how does it work
どのように機能しますか
We can use this criminology master He
私たちはこの犯罪学の達人、彼を使うことができます。
Talk about discussing three criteria to see the situation at that time
その時の状況を見るための3つの基準について議論するという話
This is called the relationship of principle
これを原理関係といいます
that is to say in the city
つまり都会では
way cities when these cut categories
これらがカテゴリーを分類するときの都市
Its laws, the rule of law, are strict enough
その法律、法の支配は十分に厳格です
In fact, through the previous discussion, we
実際、前回の議論を通じて、
already visible
すでに見えています
Actually, I think it's something that can't be said
実際は何とも言えない事だと思います
Yeah
うん
right
右
sound is great
音は素晴らしいです
so i think there is also
だからそれもあると思います
I think in terms of severity
重症度から考えると
We can see the green beauty in the Qing Dynasty
清朝の緑の美しさを見ることができます
Whether it is green or beautiful
緑だったり綺麗だったり
Luli is also good
ルリさんもいいですね
In fact, the specification for cutting
実はカットの仕様は
and come true are very subtle
そしてcome trueは非常に微妙です
So in terms of severity
したがって、重症度の観点から言えば、
OK, he has such an effect
OK、彼にはそのような効果があります
But then the swiftness
しかしその後の素早さは
what is rapidity
迅速性とは何ですか
In modern terms, it is called quick trial and quick decision
現代風に言えば、迅速裁判・迅速決定ということです。
Which means after today's crime
つまり、今日の犯罪の後
you caught the criminal
あなたは犯人を捕まえました
Is it going to be a quick trial?
クイックトライアルになるのでしょうか？
But we see a lot of these suspects get caught
しかし、これらの容疑者の多くが逮捕されるのを私たちは見ています
In fact, your case still can't be used later.
実際、あなたのケースはまだ後で使用できません。
Why? Because many cases are in the process of expedited trial and trial
その理由は、多くの事件が迅速な審理と裁判の進行中であるためです。
took a long time
長い時間がかかりました
Sometimes these cuts to the suspect
時々、これらは容疑者に切り込みます
After being caught, he said that he had an accomplice
逮捕後、彼はカジュアルな共犯者がいると述べた
Then we can't catch those accomplices anyway
それでは共犯者を捕まえることはできません
I feel like this case has been extended and there is no way to solve it.
この事件は延長され、解決する方法がないように感じます。
So there is a little bit of a problem in terms of speed.
したがって、速度の点で少し問題があります。
As for what this certainty refers to
この確実性が何を指すのかというと、
that is to say a criminal
つまり犯罪者です
When a crime can be sure soon
犯罪後はすぐに確実に
suffered rumors
噂に苦しんだ
this punishment
この罰
But we also saw earlier
しかし、私たちは以前にも見ました
In fact, to be honest
実際、正直に言うと
So its detection rate is 28 percent
つまり、検出率は 28 パーセントです
That is to say, more than 80% of people who commit crimes cannot be caught.
つまり、犯罪を犯しても8割以上の人は捕まらないのです。
it can escape
それは逃げることができる
it can get away with it
それはそれで済ますことができる
Then from this certainty, it is not enough
そして、この確信からは、それだけでは十分ではありません
So from this point of view
したがって、この観点からすると
The Qing Dynasty as a whole was at least sustaining its own business
清朝は全体として、少なくとも独自の事業を維持していました
it's in the punitive crime
それは懲罰的犯罪の範囲内です
even though it has strict regulations
厳しい規制があるにもかかわらず
But it can't tell the truth
でもそれは真実を語ることはできない
Its detection rate is also very limited
検出率も非常に限られています
So take the protection of China
だから中国の保護を受けてください
So-called local law cannot be enforced
いわゆる現地法は施行できない
you continue to have the law
あなたには法律があり続けます
You can't really have these mechanisms related to the housing market
住宅市場に関連するこれらのメカニズムは実際にはあり得ません
Such a law is still empty
そんな法律は未だに空虚である
no way housing market true crime
まさかの住宅市場本当の犯罪
That's what I'm going to do for you today
それが今日私があなたのためにやることです
Welcome everyone to listen to advice
皆さんもアドバイスを聞いてください
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました
I think when everyone heard this story just now, it was very vivid and interesting.
皆さんも今この話を聞いて、とても生々しくて面白かったと思います。
I think we, the audience, have questions. If you ask questions, welcome to ask them at this time.
私たち聴衆からも質問があると思いますが、もし質問があれば、この時間に質問してください。
Does anyone want to ask some further questions?
さらに質問したい人はいますか?
well, this gentleman is at the end
さて、この紳士は最後です
Okay, Im sorry, thats what I just wanted to do in the process
わかりました、ごめんなさい、それが途中でやりたかったことです
That is to say, there are some disruptions in the market or the situation that the teacher just mentioned is early and strong.
つまり、市場に混乱が生じている、あるいは今先生がおっしゃったような状況が早くて強い。
Is that the markets in various cities during the climax just now?
先ほどのクライマックスの各都市の市場でしょうか？
Does their house look like a phenomenon?
彼らの家は現象のように見えますか？
Thanks
ありがとう
"Cao Chao Traveler"
《曹超旅人》
The villain is called Weasley Slatto
悪役の名前はウィーズリー・スラット
And there's a scene in it that's Wesley Slaytoo
その中にウェスリー・スレイトゥーのシーンがあります
when he arrives in the future
彼が未来に到着したとき
He wants to test the power of future police policing
彼は将来の警察の取り締まりの力を試したいと考えている
He saw a car on the street
彼は通りで車を見た
He knocked on that car window
彼は車の窓をノックした
He figured he had the police coming
彼は警察が来ると思った
After a long time, the police still haven't come
長い時間が経っても警察は来ません
He knocks on the second window
彼は2番目の窓をノックする
forget it
忘れてください
not yet
まだ
He said he was too good
彼は自分が良すぎると言った
this is my heaven
ここは私の天国です
is my crime paradise
私の犯罪天国です
This is actually another crime theory.
これは実際には別の犯罪理論です。
present in the movie
映画の中に存在する
But I think the broken gut theory makes sense
でも、腸が壊れた理論は理にかなっていると思う
But used in the history of Ming and Qing Dynasties
しかし、明と清の時代の歴史では使用されました
Especially in terms of the history of the Qing Dynasty
特に清朝の歴史に関しては
more difficult to use
比較難用
Because to be honest, this gut-breaking theory
正直に言うと、この根性論は
is a very modern theory
それは非常に現代的な理論です
very modern theory
非常に現代的な理論
Especially in modern urbanized buildings
特に現代の都市化された建物では
will use
使用します
This traditional Chinese building
この伝統的な中国の建物
buildings in the city
街中の建物
Actually window
実は窓
There are few windows in the city
街には窓が少ない
because most of the computer
なぜなら、ほとんどのコンピュータは
So the computer arrives this evening
それで今夜コンピューターが到着します
It's actually made of wood planks to keep the wind up.
実は風を防ぐために木でできているんです。
So usually when you go to steal a computer
したがって、通常、コンピュータを盗みに行くときは、
you have to use another method
別の方法を使用する必要があります
just put it that
それを言ってください
this is one way
これは一方通行です
The second way is to climb the wall
2番目の方法は壁を登ることです
climb to the second floor of it
その2階に登ってください
Because the first floor of the traditional Chinese shop
伝統中華のお店の1階なので
it is two layers
それは二層です
Chinese traditional shop is two floors
中国伝統店は2階建て
The first floor is sealed with wooden boards
1階は木の板で密閉されています
When the official gate is sealed with wooden boards
官門を木板で封鎖した場合
But there are windows on the second floor
でも2階にも窓はあるよ
call skylight
天窓に電話をかける
So the second way is you climb the skylight
2番目の方法は天窓に登ることです
Go to the second floor to draw the machine
2階に行ってマシンを描く
So many shops were stolen
たくさんのお店が盗まれました
Usually in addition to being knocked into the pot by the wall
通常、壁にぶつかってポットに衝突することに加えて、
is knocking on the door
ドアがノックされましたか
Someone climbed to the skylight
誰かが天窓に登った
Go in through the skylight on the second floor to smoke something
2階の天窓から入って何か吸う
So why didn't I use the inside of the broken window
ではなぜ割れた窓の内側を使わなかったのか
The reason is because there is no suitable
理由は適当なものが無いから
Because there is a more modern version of this objection in the broken window
なぜなら、割れた窓にはこの反論のより現代的なバージョンがあるからです。
So in the traditional Chinese period
したがって、伝統的な中国の時代には
There is no way to explain it this way
このように説明する方法はありません
Because the traditional Chinese architecture was different at that time
当時の中国の伝統的な建築は異なっていたため
so it counts
だからそれは重要です
That's it, thank you
それです、ありがとう
lady please sit down
女性、座ってください
May I ask, was Xiao Cong a local at that time?
聞いてもいいですか、シャオコンは当時地元の人でしたか？
ok very good please sit down please sit down
わかりました、とてもいいです、座ってください、座ってください
In fact, I say this, you Chongqing as an example
実際、私は重慶を例としてこれを言います。
In fact, why is urbanization so serious?
実際、なぜ都市化はこれほど深刻なのでしょうか?
I would ask why the urbanization is growing so fast in 19
なぜ19年にこれほど急速に都市化が進んでいるのかを尋ねたいと思います。
In fact, urbanites are not particularly good at living
実際のところ、都会人は特に生活が上手というわけではありません
No, urbanites are especially good at giving birth, and there are so many children at once
いいえ、都会人は特に出産が得意で、一度にたくさんの子供が生まれます。
In fact, most of them are foreigners who came here to find work and do business.
実際、彼らのほとんどは仕事を探したりビジネスをするためにここに来た外国人です。
So most of them are foreigners
なのでほとんどが外国人です
Well, actually head inside, and then build the hut inside
さて、実際に中に入って、その中に小屋を建てます
There is quite a field house
かなりのフィールドハウスがあります
quite a field
かなりの畑
The proportion of local discoveries is certainly not low
ローカルな発見の割合は決して低くない
But for the first time I said there might be half etiquette too
でも初めて言った、半分エチケットもあるかもしれないって
Other counties and cities
他の郡や市
I can't count
数えられない
Because there was no way to do this statistics at that time.
当時はこの統計を行う方法がなかったからです。
but we say for sure
しかし、私たちは確かに言います
People from other counties and cities
他の郡や都市から来た人々
As a child's travel port high
お子様の旅行ポートハイとして
And what?
そして何？
i mentioned earlier
先ほども言いましたが
Many were poor when they were young
貧しい子供たちがたくさんいる
then get together
それから集まってください
Everyone started to vote
みんな投票し始めた
in that case
その場合
Many of these people are foreigners
この人達の多くは外国人です
are foreigners
外国人です
because of the words of the locals
地元の人の言葉のせいで
he usually doesn't follow
彼は通常フォローしません
Not so many people gather together
そんなに人が集まらない
usually foreigners
普通に外国人
Find those crackpots and get together over there
おかしな奴らを見つけて、あそこに集まろう
Therefore, the travel port of foreigners is high.
そのため外国人の渡航港が多い。
But this will lead to
しかし、これは次のことにつながります
The first is actually something that modern criminology pays great attention to.
1 つ目は、実際、現代の犯罪学が非常に注目しているものです。
A problem of great concern in criminology
犯罪学において非常に懸念される問題
that is
あれは
Immigration is a disruption of social order
移民は社会秩序の破壊である
an important information
重要な情報
Of course the immigration
もちろん入国審査も
Comparison is no longer imaging immigrants
比較はもはや移民をイメージするものではない
more like immigrant
むしろ移民っぽい
Immigrants from other provinces
他県からの移民
but
しかし
The perspective of traditional officials
伝統的な官僚の視点
They do feel that aliens are coming
彼らは宇宙人がやってくると感じている
dangerous
危険
But they will also know that they can't call out the translator all at once
しかし、彼らは同時に通訳を呼び出すことができないことも理解するでしょう。
Because in fact, many people from other places come to do business
実際、他所からビジネスに来る人も多いので
or they have a professional job
あるいは専門的な仕事をしている
so this
したがって、この
So the official
それで公式は
one thing they must say
彼らが言わなければならないことが一つある
Chongqing this place
重慶のこの場所
Wufang Zazu
五方雜祖
What's the meaning
どのような意味です
It's from all over the place
それはあちこちから来ています
So easy to grow and work
成長も働きもとても簡単
things are vague
物事が曖昧だ
mean to say
言う意味
Chongqing because many people from other places do business here
他の場所から多くの人がここでビジネスをしているため、重慶
So there are also many big buyers
大手の買い手も多いので
There are quite a few people who come to the world to touch
世界に触れるために来る人はかなりいます
Master thinks this means
マスターはこれが意味すると考えています
So the father of information or current management
つまり、情報または現在の経営の父
Actually realize these things
これらのことを実際に実現してください
So we still have to implement
したがって、まだ実装する必要があります
who is supporting
誰がサポートしているのか
So under this circumstance, I can answer you, the proportion of outside points is actually quite high, which is equal to how many times the proportion reaches this time, it is difficult to estimate
この状況では、お答えしますが、実際には外側のポイントの割合が非常に高く、これは今回の割合が何倍に達するかに相当します。推定するのは困難です。
hope to answer you
あなたに答えられることを願っています
Thank you, Ms. Bai Yurure, are you familiar with it?
バイユレさん、ありがとうございます、ご存知ですか？
i heard what do you think
どう思いますか？
What do you think, first in US M crams
どう思いますか、まずは米国のM塾で
In the store, I ask you to search
店内で検索してみてください
output this now'll
これを出力します
Grab steep C mass ai
急勾配のCマスaiを掴む
Looking at the street will return to the old days
街並みを見れば昔に戻る
Could you please check
確認していただけますか
The data searched is
検索されたデータは、
$950
＄９５０
is $500
500ドルです
you can search
検索できます
search
検索
What do you think
どう思いますか
well , actually your question is very meaningful
そうですね、実際あなたの質問は非常に意味のあるものです
very interesting
とても興味深い
But since you ask the question now is the question now
でも、あなたが質問するからには、今が質問なのです
I put this problem in the Qing Dynasty
私はこの問題を清朝に置きました
The Qing Dynasty, especially the issue you mentioned later
清朝、特に後で言及した問題
In this way, I may not be able to answer your previous questions.
このため、以前のご質問にはお答えできない場合がございます。
But the problem behind you is
しかし、あなたの背後にある問題は
For example, now there are many refugees
例えば、今は難民がたくさんいます。
he might grab something
彼は何かを掴むかもしれない
he may not feel that he
彼はそう感じていないかもしれない
What do you know about Xiao Bingmo
シャオ・ビンモについて何を知っていますか
grab something
何かを掴む
He may not think he is gay
彼は自分が同性愛者であるとは思っていないかもしれない
But it was like this when I was a child
でも子供の頃はこんな感じだった
that there is an objection in tradition
伝統に異議があること
social objection
社会的反対
What is social opposition
社会的反対とは何ですか
so
それで
in traditional Chinese
繁体字中国語で
Our general family will only go outside the iron
私たち一般家族は鉄の外にしか出ません
There may be some mountains nearby
近くに山があるかもしれない
some mountains
いくつかの山
There will be wood down the mountain
山の下には木があるだろう
common people think
庶民は考える
I go to the nearby mountains
近くの山に行きます
cut trees, cut moss
木を切る、苔を切る
it's not illegal
それは違法ではありません
social crime
社会犯罪
but
しかし
in fact not necessarily so
実際には必ずしもそうではありません
because at that time
なぜならその時は
woods on many hills or these
多くの丘やこれらの上の森
it is kind
優しいですね
so
それで
that's how it's generally said
一般的にはそう言われています
there are many people when
人がたくさんいるとき
So in the Qing Dynasty
それで清の時代には
Even when it was Trump
トランプのときも
some people he thinks
彼が思う何人かの人々
he took something today
彼は今日何かを持って行きました
i do something
私は何かをします
Does not involve legal same-sex issues
法的な同性愛問題を含まない
But legally speaking
しかし法的に言えば
He's actually gay
彼は実は同性愛者だ
So that means
つまり、
a matter of habit
習慣の問題
That is to say, you follow the wind is a habit today
つまり、風に従うのが今日の習慣です
he thinks
彼が考えている
giving some example
いくつかの例を挙げて
I'm following a certain wind habit
私はある風の習慣に従っています
I went through a today
私は今日を経験しました
land
陸上
see this
これを見てください
There are apples and orange barrels on the nearby tree
近くの木にリンゴとオレンジの樽があります
There is a conceptual contradiction
概念的な矛盾がある
some people think it's a habit
それが習慣だと思う人もいる
it does not involve legal issues
法的な問題は関係ありません
But legally it's a steal
でも法的には窃盗だよ
It involves you stealing someone's belongings
他人の持ち物を盗む行為です
all items
全てのアイテム
There will be such a contradictory character
こんな矛盾したキャラもいるだろう
Happens in many things whether present or traditional
現在のものであろうと伝統的なものであろうと、多くのもので起こります
This notion is sometimes
この概念は時々
Some contradictions and overlaps
いくつかの矛盾と重複
so that it will cause
それが引き起こすように
inside the objection
反論の中で
The person involved really thinks he is a criminal
関係者は本気で自分が犯罪者だと思っている
Because he is in his traditional concept
なぜなら彼は伝統的な概念を貫いているからです
He thinks his stuff is from himself
彼は自分のものは自分から来たものだと思っている
His so-called social crimes
彼のいわゆる社会犯罪
Then what do you say about this thing?
では、このことについてどう思いますか？
For example, I said how to change
たとえば、どのように変更するかを言いました。
It's actually hard for me to answer Li Zhi's question
李志の質問に答えるのは実は難しい
Because this according to historians also
歴史家によればこれは
not a chinese historian
中国の歴史家ではありません
is a historian of european studies
ヨーロッパ研究の歴史家です
criminal history
犯罪歴
study this so-called social crime
このいわゆる社会犯罪を研究してください
He thinks that many behaviors
彼は、多くの行動が、
Traditionally, it is not a crime
伝統的には犯罪ではない
But because a few rich people
でも裕福な人が少ないから
In order to protect his assets
彼の財産を守るために
He gives power to the law
彼は法に力を与える
make these behaviors
こういった行動をする
crimes against the property of vietnamese people
ベトナム人の財産に対する犯罪
So the process of law formation
つまり、法律形成のプロセスは、
There are a lot of vested interests
既得権益が多い
or a mechanism set up by the rich to protect himself
あるいは富裕層が自分を守るために設けた仕組み
Then many ordinary people and their families are easy to offend when they dont know about it.
そして、多くの一般人やその家族は、それを知らないと簡単に気分を害してしまいます。
But his own person is not a crime
でも彼自身は犯罪ではない
In terms of European history, there are such studies
ヨーロッパの歴史に関しては、このような研究があります
However, such research may draw criticism from other scholars.
ただし、そのような研究は他の学者から批判を受ける可能性があります。
That is, how do you know the criminals and their confessions
つまり、どうやって犯人とその自白を知ることができるのでしょうか？
say we know i thought it was tradition
知っていると言ってください、それが伝統だと思っていました
This is possible
これは可能です
How can you be sure that the reason these people are giving is not an excuse
この人たちが言っている理由が言い訳ではないとどうやって確信できるのですか？
In other words, he deliberately found an excuse
言い換えれば、彼は意図的に言い訳を見つけた
So he clearly knew it was a crime
だから彼はそれが犯罪であることを明らかに知っていた
he found an excuse
彼は言い​​訳を見つけた
This is actually a bit like many communication people in China want to steal
これは実際、中国の多くの人々が盗もうとしている通信に似ています。
He actually stole something he'd been stealing for maybe 50 years
彼は実際、おそらく50年間盗んでいたものを盗んだ
Might actually ask him how much you stole
実際に彼にいくら盗んだのか聞いてみるかもしれない
how much did you steal like this
こんなに盗んだのいくらですか
He just said I stole a little bit
彼は私が少し盗んだと言ったところです
I stole everything else
他のものはすべて盗んだ
Because he if I come out
なぜなら、私が出てくると彼は
he stole it all
彼はすべてを盗んだ
then not the most followed
それでは最もフォローされていません
then he might say
そうすれば彼は言うかもしれない
He also didn't steal it from me
彼も私からそれを盗んだわけではありません
are stolen
盗まれています
Or I just picked it up
それとも拾っただけなのか
i don't know what this is
これが何なのか分かりません
or some people
または何人かの人々
he accepts a dirt
彼は汚れを受け入れます
pick up dirt these people
この人たちの汚れを拾う
buy dirt these people
この人たちの汚れを買う
then he will say
そうすれば彼は言うだろう
i didn't know it was dirt
汚れだとは知りませんでした
But I still spent so much money to buy
でも、それでも買うのに大金を使った
good
良い
This is my current unit
これが私の現在のユニットです
How is it usually found that such a situation
このような状況は通常どのようにして発見されるのでしょうか
his method of punishment
彼の懲罰方法
In fact it's still too early
実はまだ早いんだよ
That is to say, those who take the dirt
つまり、汚れを取る者は、
Although you become saying
ってなってしまうけど
i didn't know it was dirt
汚れだとは知りませんでした
But you still have to put the dirt in a root
でも根の中に土を入れないといけない
so the guy who bought the dirt
それで土を買った奴は
whether he knows or not
彼が知っているかどうかは別として
I know when I'm gone
いつ私がいなくなるか知っています
finally got caught
ついに捕まった
you are not worth the principle
あなたには原則に値しない
going back
戻る
So according to the actual marriage of the Seven Dynasties and the appearance of the bookstore
実際の七王朝の結婚と書店の外観によると
I hope a little bit will answer some of your questions
あなたの質問のいくつかに少しでも答えられれば幸いです
But because my research is history
しかし、私の研究は歴史に残るものであるため、
Contemporary issues may be more appropriate for contemporary qualifications
現代の問題は現代の資格に適している可能性があります
Hope to answer some of your questions
いくつかの質問にお答えできれば幸いです
Thanks
ありがとう
Then this classmate first ask Cai Yunfeng
そこでこのクラスメートはまず蔡雲峰に尋ねます。
Hello Professor
こんにちは教授
then i have two questions
それから質問が2つあります
The first question is about the criminal data and documents mentioned above.
最初の質問は、上記の犯罪データと文書についてです。
It is clearer than Qianlong's arrival
乾隆帝の到着より明らかだ
It is the words of the seven dynasties from the front to the back
表から裏まで七王朝の言葉です
His data is slowly increasing
彼のデータは徐々に増加しています
That number is because
その数字の理由は、
The more you go to the region and modern or modern
地方に行けば行くほど、近現代に行けば行くほど
Then his documents will be better preserved.
そうすれば彼の文書はより良く保存されるでしょう。
That's why the majority
だからこそ大多数は
The second question is
2番目の質問は、
Like ancient times, whether it is the Qing Dynasty or earlier
清の時代であろうとそれ以前であろうと、古代のように
That kind of comparison details
そのような比較の詳細
Then folk clerical data
それから民俗事務資料
If he
もし彼が
take this secret
この秘密をとってください
that is
あれは
For example, in local government offices
たとえば、地方自治体の役所では、
still say yes
まだ「はい」と言う
Send it from the beginning to the center to keep it
最初からセンターに送って保管してください
because
なぜなら
i would like to say
言いたいです
If you do research later
後で調べたら
He'll need some data and facts
彼にはいくつかのデータと事実が必要だ
then he will come out of him
そうすれば彼は彼から出てくるでしょう
ok thanks professor
わかりました、ありがとう教授
very good question
とても良い質問
Apparently this gentleman has quite an understanding of this stuff
どうやらこの紳士はこの件についてかなり理解しているようです
Actually it is
実はそうなんです
In these judicial files leaked by the local Zhou
地元の周氏が漏洩したこれらの司法ファイルでは、
He is roughly divided into two
彼は大きく二つに分けられる
For example, we can roughly divide it into two
例えば、大きく2つに分けることができます。
Two categories of this justice
この正義の 2 つのカテゴリー
sin of crime
犯罪の罪
intermarriage iron
結婚鉄
probably
おそらく
so-called marriage-related
いわゆる結婚関係
It's related to the division of this land.
それはこの土地の分割に関係している。
Half of this type of intermarriage
このタイプの結婚の半分は
now let's talk
さあ話しましょう
may be inferior to so-called civil cases
いわゆる民事訴訟より劣るかもしれない
this civil case
この民事訴訟
Usually its OK after Zhou Xieguan finishes the sentence
通常は周謝関が文章を書き終えた後でも大丈夫です
he doesn't have to report to that
彼はそこに報告する必要はない
above officials
役人以上
Master Ah Xiang
マスター・アー・シャン
then the center does not
そうすればセンターはそうではありません
it's ok
大丈夫です
Another kind of case is called secret channel serious case
別の種類の事件は秘密チャンネル重大事件と呼ばれます
The Case of the Dead Man's Robber
死者強盗事件
This is the more important case
これはより重要なケースです
after this case
この事件の後
after your previous trial
前回のトライアルの後
You still send it all the way to the center
まだセンターまで送ってるのね
Especially the death penalty has to be sent to the Criminal Bureau
特に死刑は刑事局に送らなければならない
this is punishment
これは罰だ
So we're left with a lot of central archives now
現在、多くの中央アーカイブが残っています
This file is called Criminal Division Basic
このファイルは刑事部門基本と呼ばれます
Probably this kind of secret case
たぶんこういう秘密事件
Then collect the central archive from the place
次に、その場所から中央アーカイブを収集します
such file
そのようなファイル
But if it is an ordinary small case
でも普通の小さなケースなら
Including this kind of Jiedao case
こういう自島事件も含めて
In fact, it's all judged locally.
実際には、すべて現地で判断されます。
so what we're left with now
それで今私たちに残っているものは
Why do local cases
なぜローカルなケースが起こるのか
we can use it for research
研究に使用できます
It is usually to study this
通常はこれを勉強することです
mutual detection
相互検出
There are also relatively small cases of fishing
比較的小規模な漁獲例もある
Everyday this small this
毎日この小さなこれ
Baptism case
洗礼事件
Then the big wash desk is out of our readjustment area
それから、大きな洗面台は再調整エリアの外にあります
but interesting
でも興味深い
you go back to your first question today
今日の最初の質問に戻ります
It's a question of cultural preservation
それは文化の保存の問題です
Will there be surplus points in its quantity?
その数量に余剰ポイントはありますか?
just because of the preservation of literacy
読み書き能力を維持するためだけに
will affect your ratio in terms of quantity
量の点で比率に影響します
Of course it will and it's obvious
もちろんそうなりますし、それは明らかです
and i say this
そして私はこう言います
I dont know if this classmate can really pass an article
このクラスメートが本当に論文を合格できるかどうかはわかりません
A few years ago there was an article in American History Month Day Together
数年前、American History Month Day Togetherに記事がありました
big dispute
大論争
That is, there are several scholars in mainland China
つまり、中国本土には数人の学者がいるということです。
Research House is a scholar
リサーチハウスは学者です
an article he wrote in english
彼が英語で書いた記事
Statistical use of the lineage system
系統システムの統計的利用
china in qing dynasty
清朝の中国
The change in the number of his violent keystrokes
激しい打鍵回数の変化
Change in the number of violent keystrokes
激しいキーストローク数の変化
Then he felt that after the conclusion
そして結論後に彼はこう感じた
Many American scholars do not believe
アメリカの学者の多くは信じていない
why not believe
なぜ信じないのか
Because he counted the numbers from the Qing Dynasty
清の時代の数字を数えたからです。
During the Xuantong period of the Qing Dynasty
清朝宣通時代
Attention everyone, when Xianfeng is in court
Xianfengが法廷にいるときはみんなに注意してください
And when the next few courts are here
そして次の数回の法廷で
central department
中央部門
Or the central habit people have been blown
あるいは、人々が吹き飛ばされてきた中心的な習慣
So its hard to talk about it. Lets talk about the period of the Taiping Heavenly Kingdom.
話が難しいので、太平天国の時代について話しましょう。
those places that happened in many war-torn areas
多くの戦争で荒廃した地域のそれらの場所
Even if there is a secret case
たとえ秘密事件があっても
These cases may be sent to the central referee
これらのケースは中央審判に送られる可能性があります
Impossible, it was all war
ありえない、すべては戦争だった
Where did you go before
前にどこに行きましたか
So such statistics will be biased.
したがって、そのような統計には偏りが生じます。
jigsaw puzzle
ジグソーパズル
His statistics are problematic
彼の統計には問題がある
there is indeed a problem
確かに問題があります
so from this point of view
したがって、この観点からすると
From this point of view, I also think
この観点から私も思うのですが、
The data in the table I just used is more reliable
先ほど使用した表のデータの方が信頼性が高くなります
Why?
なぜ？
Because there is no Taiping Heavenly Kingdom period near this place
この近くには太平天国時代はないので
not actually affected by his
実際には彼の影響を受けていない
The actual impact of the war
戦争の実際の影響
So the stat I used
それで、私が使用した統計
So this statistic
したがって、この統計は
Their number may be more representative than that of the Central Bank
彼らの数字は中央銀行の数字よりも代表的かもしれない
more likely to reflect certain trends
特定の傾向を反映する可能性が高い
Well, this is my future research.
まあ、これは私の今後の研究です。
not reached yet
まだ届いていない
So in the future I will mention
したがって、将来的には言及します
But the problem with this conclusion is very good
しかし、この結論の問題は非常に良いです
good professor
教授好
Most of what the conclusion hearer hears is crime
結論を聞く人が聞くことのほとんどは犯罪です
Most of what is heard is cut to
聞こえてくるもののほとんどはカットされています
right
右
Then I'm more curious about
それから私はもっと興味があります
Of course after the crime it's about solving the case.
もちろん、犯罪が起こった後は事件を解決することになります。
I see that kind of crime in the next year on being gay
来年には同性愛者であることを理由にしたそのような犯罪が起こるだろう
Of course he is down
もちろん彼は落ち込んでいる
But it's cut at a glance
でも一目で切れる
But I'd rather know if it's a murder case
でもそれが殺人事件かどうか知りたい
homicide
殺人
That is to say, the murder part
つまり殺人パート
He has many possibilities for the past in ancient times
彼は古代の過去について多くの可能性を持っています
historical time
歴史的な時間
How did he solve the murder case?
彼はどのようにして殺人事件を解決したのでしょうか?
Also, does he have any tricks?
また、彼には何かコツがあるのでしょうか？
yes can share with us
はい、私たちと共有できます
I think it must be interesting
きっと面白いと思うよ
I rarely see that in books
本では滅多に見ないけど
And the second one is that I direct something
2つ目は、私が何かを監督するということです
For example, like a few Tao Chaos before
たとえば、以前のいくつかのタオカオスのように
There will always be so-called Enemy Festival detectives
いわゆる敵祭り探偵は常に存在します
what we know
私たちが知っていること
We read what kind of detectives he had in the Ming and Qing Dynasties
明と清の時代に彼がどのような探偵をしていたのかを読んでみましょう
can point us a bit
少し教えてください
The more interesting part
さらに興味深い部分
Thank you, teacher
ありがとう、先生
ok thank you for the question
わかりました、質問ありがとうございます
But this question was originally my biggest answer
しかし、この質問はもともと私の最大の答えでした
real
本物
Because usually history if you don't read
読まないと普通歴史になるから
If you study these things yourself
こういうことを自分で勉強したら
we dare not say too much
私たちはあまり多くを言うつもりはありません
because like secret case
秘密の事件みたいだから
You can see this statistic
この統計を見ることができます
The statistics of the part of the secret case in this quantity
この量の秘密ケースの部分の統計
not too little
少なすぎない
For example, the secret case of Comrade Chaoyou Basic Middle
たとえば、朝友基本中同志の秘密事件
put it in this
これに入れてください
But this secret case is not
しかし、この秘密事件はそうではありません
Everything we imagined was a secret case
私たちが想像していたものはすべて秘密の事件だった
I don't want to be involved in this secret case
この秘密事件には関わりたくない
Also includes unmanned entities found
発見された無人エンティティも含まれます
There are quite a few such proportions
そういう割合は結構あるよ
So in fact, this still needs further research.
したがって、実際には、これにはまださらなる研究が必要です。
usually
いつもの
Secret cases will of course have subsidies and autopsies
極秘事件にはもちろん補助金や解剖もある
these will have it
これらはそれを持っています
Details of these techniques and studies
これらの技術と研究の詳細
It is also worth doing research
研究する価値もあります
But this part is not our specialty
しかし、この部分は私たちの専門ではありません
What we call for young researchers
若手研究者に求めるもの
He actually studies this type of
彼は実際にこの種のことを研究しています
So maybe his future
それでおそらく彼の将来は
He also belongs to one of the studies
彼もまた研究の一つに属している
So future publication of his research would
したがって、彼の研究が将来出版されることになるでしょう。
should be able to see
見えるはずです
can have some answers
いくつかの答えがあるかもしれない
In addition, the detective
さらに探偵は、
actually
実際
should say this
これを言うべきです
Taihan is like a god official
タイハンは神の役人のようなものです
because of this
このため
It's hard for us to see the valley of the gods
神々の谷を見るのは難しい
what about these things
これらのことはどうですか
Some people just want to write lyrics after all
結局歌詞を書きたいだけの人もいる
who knows
知るか
Many officials are like this
公務員ってこういう人多いよな
his magistrate
彼の判事
then trial
それから裁判
He feels very expressive
彼はとても表現力豊かだと感じます
He thinks he is very Thai and like a god
彼は自分がとてもタイ人で神のようだと思っています
Usually he writes in his essay
通常、彼はエッセイにこう書いています
will leave these judgments
これらの判断を放棄します
He feels very proud of the sentences he passed.
彼は自分が下した判決をとても誇りに思っている。
He will leave his sentencing process behind
彼は量刑プロセスを放置するだろう
This will appear in many people's articles
多くの人の記事に登場します
I dare not say who is a political judge
誰が政治裁判官なのかあえて言いません
Or an official who judges a case like a trial
または裁判などの事件を裁く役人
But many of these officials left behind
しかし、これらの役人の多くは後に残しました
probably to show
おそらく見せるため
I'm pretty good at judging.
私は判断力がかなり優れています。
verdict
評決
Indeed, if you look at these
確かに、これらを見てみると、
You'll find these officials adjudicating
これらの役人が裁定を行っているのがわかるでしょう
There are really five sets
本当は5セットあるよ
He found another suspicious place
彼はまた怪しい場所を見つけた
If we look at the actual case
実際の事例を見てみると
From Guo Han to the actual case
郭漢から実際の事件まで
Niu Yize's case left a deep impression on us
牛宜澤さんの事件は私たちに深い印象を残しました
there is a personal reporter
個人記者がいる
He said how many pieces of clothes were stolen from my house
彼は私の家から何枚の服が盗まれたかと言った
Then privately vote how many pieces
次に、何個かを個人的に投票します
still how so how
まだどうやって、どうやって
Officials came to see the benefactor
役人が恩人に会いに来た
just feel
ただ感じてください
That is to say, you are definitely a fake
つまり君は間違いなく偽物だ
so as to get outside
外に出るように
Because the official looked directly at the Wu wearing
役人が着ている呉を直視したため
If you can collect such precious things at home today
そんな大切なものを今日お家で集められたら
Why Wushu is such a simple martial art
武術がなぜこれほどシンプルな武術なのか
So he can conclude except from the very beginning
したがって、彼は最初から以外は結論を下すことができます
You are a slander
あなたは誹謗中傷者です
it's none of those things
それはどれでもない
is pretending
ふりをしている
And by the way I also...
そしてちなみに私も…
because here
ここだから
I also say by the way
ちなみに私も言います
i see a lot of love child inside
私は心の中にたくさんの愛の子がいるのが見えます
many stolen maharajas
盗まれた多くのマハラジャ
if female
女性の場合
are all women
全員女性です
And because the ex-wife is very rich
そして元妻は大金持ちなので
so i keep joking about this
だから私はこのことについて冗談を言い続けています
When I saw this, I verified a statement from some historiography
これを見たとき、私はある歴史学の記述を確認しました
Talk about why many women in the folk want to be widows
民衆の多くの女性が未亡人になりたがる理由について話す
Because they said that this place is also Rational choice
ここも合理的な選択だと言っていたから
Yes, it's physical choice
はい、それは物理的な選択です
Why?
なぜ？
Because according to the Chinese law at that time
当時の中国の法律によると
if you are used to it
慣れていれば
if you speed up
スピードを上げると
After the husband passes away, if you dare to marry someone as a wife, your original husband's property will no longer be lost, and the marriage partner you originally brought will also be gone.
夫が亡くなった後、あえて誰かと妻として結婚すれば、元の夫の財産は失われなくなり、元々連れてきた結婚相手もいなくなります。
That's why many women prefer to be widowed. When I was widowed, my husband's family was still mine, and the marriages I brought were still mine, and I was still mine. The big deal is to leave it to me, this is if I dare to marry, I have nothing.
私が未亡人になったときも、夫の家族は依然として私のものであり、私がもたらした結婚も依然として私のものであり、私は依然として私のものでした。大事なのは私に任せることだ、もし私が結婚する勇気があるなら、私には何もない。
So many people say, why there are so many widows today, and there are so many widows who are really graduates and law-abiding widows, is related to this rational right.
明日、なぜこれほど多くの未亡人がいるのか、そして本当に卒業生で法律を遵守している未亡人がこれほどたくさんいるのは、この合理的な権利に関係している、と多くの人が言います。
I said, at least from what I saw in this case, it is true that many of the stolen women were widows and married, and I did not marry in vain.
私は、少なくともこの事件で私が見た限りでは、略奪された女性の多くが未亡人で既婚者であることは事実であり、私の結婚は無駄ではなかった、と言いました。
But when they sell newspapers, they talk about women, I am so pitiful, I have been a widow all my life, even if I have a little suspicion, I will be stolen into women, but you can see that she has a lot of marriages.
でも、彼らが新聞を売るとき、彼らは女性のことを話します、私はとても哀れです、私は生涯未亡人でした、たとえ少しの疑いを持っていても、私は女性に盗まれます、しかし、彼女はたくさんのことを持っていることがわかります結婚。
Likewise, many people are widows.
同様に、未亡人になる人もたくさんいます。
So the scholars behind it still have what they say
つまり、その背後にある学者たちはまだ彼らの言うことを持っています
I am a reader of everything
私はあらゆるものを読む人です
all my life
私の人生のうちで
Wow how to live at home
うわー、家でどうやって暮らすか
But you find that the things behind the house are still valuable
でも、家の後ろにあるものはまだ価値があることに気づきました
a lot of money
たくさんのお金
So Nusheng is writing Zhuangzi or everyone knows
つまり、ヌーシェンが『荘子』を書いているのか、それとも誰もが知っているのか
How much effort is spent when writing Zhuangzi
『荘子』を書くのにどれだけの労力がかかるか
Anyway, if the scene is not accepted
とにかくそのシーンが受け入れられない場合
that's not good
それは良いことではありません
So many people did not have the so-called shouchi at that time
当時、いわゆるショーチを持っていない人が非常に多かった
So I was still writing Zhuangzi
それで私はまだ『荘子』を書いていました
Not Zhou Xingzi's era
周星子の時代ではない
Designation of Zhou Xingzi's age
周星子の年齢指定
This shouchi basic writing method is writing Zhuangzi
この書知の基本的な書き方は荘子を書くことです。
you really
あなたは本当に
I
私
can i ask this question
この質問をしてもいいですか
our next last question
次の最後の質問
Let the gentleman at A3 ask first
まずはA3の紳士に聞いてみましょう
Dear Teacher Gu
親愛なるグ先生へ
Ladies and gentlemen, everyone
ご列席の皆様、皆様
Li Longzhang of the Qing Dynasty wanted to organize the subsequent Jinghui in Beiliang
清朝の李龍章は、その後の景会を北梁で組織したいと考えていた。
He does a sex act
彼は性行為をします
If we talk about the guilt at that time
あの時の罪悪感を語れば
Is there a redemption situation
償還状況はありますか
Is to use nutrition to redeem
栄養を使って償還することです
How much nutrition can be used to atone for a country change?
国の変化を償うためにどれだけの栄養を使用できるでしょうか?
Thanks
ありがとう
thank you sir
ありがとうございます
this question is important
この質問は重要です
But I can only say that I am not specialized in research
ただ、私は研究の専門家ではないとしか言​​えません
I have a postdoc
ポスドクがいる
The graduate of the University of Architecture is called KIM
建築大学の卒業生はKIMと呼ばれます
he is doing this now
彼は今これをやっています
Generally speaking, let me explain a little bit
一般的に、少し説明しましょう
This crime in China is treason
中国のこの犯罪は国家反逆罪だ
common crime
よくある犯罪
That is to say, what sentence have you been sentenced to?
つまり、あなたはどのような刑に処せられましたか？
but you can spend money
でもお金を使うことはできる
It's a vulgar crime that can be exonerated
それは無罪になる可能性のある卑劣な犯罪です
Then at this time in the Ming Dynasty
そして明のこの頃、
such sinful videos
あんな罪深い動画
Everyone can use vulgar crimes
誰でも卑劣な犯罪を利用できる
may not be sentenced directly
直接処罰されないかもしれない
It is also a serious crime
それも重大な犯罪です
But the Qing Dynasty is different
しかし清朝は違う
Since the Qing Dynasty, many criminal laws
清朝以来、多くの刑法が制定されました。
is a veritable conviction
まさに確信です
You are going to study this criminal law
あなたはこの刑法を勉強するつもりです
It's hard for you to sign it with money
お金でサインするのは難しい
So this is obviously in the Qing Dynasty
これは明らかに清朝のものです
Compared with the Ming Dynasty
明代と比べて
it changes the actual
それは実際を変える
Then when it came to the middle and late Qing Dynasty
そして清朝中期から後期になると、
Because the country's finances are poor
国の財政が悪いから
So many so-called donations
いわゆる寄付金が多すぎる
Or there are a lot of cases of bureaucrats
あるいは官僚の場合が多い
There are many cases of vulgar crimes
卑劣な犯罪が多発している
That's because the central government is short of money
それは中央政府が金欠だからだ
He hopes to use the money to supplement
彼はそのお金を補うために使いたいと考えています
will become more and more complicated
ますます複雑になります
will become more and more inconvenient
ますます不便になります
But this atonement situation
しかし、この償いの状況
if put in this steal
この盗みに入れば
rare
レア
Why?
なぜ？
because I just mentioned
先ほど言ったので
who actually stole
実際に盗んだのは誰ですか
most of the family
家族のほとんどが
Let's live these
これらを生きていきましょう
Restraint next time
次回は自粛してね
otherwise
さもないと
Although there are occupations
職業もあるのに
Although there is an identity
アイデンティティはあるのに
But it's not necessarily a person who spends a lot of money
でも、必ずしもお金をたくさん使う人というわけではありません
So usually this
それで通常はこれ
steal love this
愛を盗んでください
seldom atonement
めったに償いをしない
Plus we just saw
さらに、ちょうど見たばかりです
the stolen thing
盗まれたもの
If the price is not high
価格が高くなければ
His luggage is heavy
彼の荷物は重いです
probably a few
おそらくいくつかの
That's twenty. Thirty is amazing.
それは20です。30はすごいです。
so usually stolen love
だからたいてい盗まれた愛
Rarely sentenced
有罪判決を受けることはほとんどない
rarely foreclosed
まれに差し押さえられる
There is a way of redemption
償還方法はある
don't bother
気にしないでください
But the question you want to know
でも、あなたが知りたい質問は、
My future postdoctoral fellow
私の将来の博士研究員
He will have some further
彼にはもう少しあるだろう
this study
この研究
very convenient
とても便利
then maybe we can
それならできるかもしれない
find a better answer
より良い答えを見つける
Thanks
ありがとう
You know that I have a little question I want to ask
ちょっと聞きたいことがあるのはご存知でしょう
You said itchy head and dirty sixty
あなたは頭がかゆい、60歳が汚いと言いました
Am I dead?
私は死んでいますか？
dirty sixty that's not pretty
汚い60代、それは美しくない
In fact, according to his law
実際、彼の法律によれば、
Does he just pat lightly?
軽く撫でるだけでしょうか？
When you are dirty and twenty or forty, you will lose your stomach
汚れて二十、四十になったら腹が減るよ
So I thought it was weird then
だからその時はおかしいと思った
this is their rule
これが彼らのルールだ
But in fact, most of the cases are actually one or two strokes
しかし実際には、ほとんどの場合は1回か2回のストロークです。
So in fact, sometimes you can't take so many photos at all.
そのため、実際には、それほど多くの写真を撮ることができない場合もあります。
And the report is in a trance
そしてレポートはトランス状態にあります
In fact, many cases cannot be solved at all.
実際には、まったく解決できないケースも少なくありません。
Yes, that is, a small head
はい、つまり頭が小さいです
even if he gets caught
たとえ彼が捕まったとしても
It's hard for him to finally get to the closing part
彼にとって最終的に最後の部分にたどり着くのは難しい
Sometimes it stays off for a long time
長時間電源が入らないこともあります
Then see me and die
それなら私を見て死んでください
Sometimes it may be possible to solve the case, probably with a small penalty
場合によっては、おそらく少額の罰金で事件を解決できる可能性があります
Then hand it over to Baojia, and hand it over to the dentist
それからBaojiaに渡し、歯医者に渡します。
control
コントロール
Then when restraining him, if he commits another crime, he will be treated with questioning
そして、彼を拘束するとき、彼が別の犯罪を犯した場合、彼は取り調べを受けます。
lock him up
彼を閉じ込める
But actually, let's just say
しかし、実際には、ただ言ってみましょう
I can't finish arresting criminals and concubines.
犯罪者と側室の逮捕が終わらない。
And the concubine actually knows the dentist himself
そして、側室は実際に歯科医自身を知っています
Many people know that Momoren is a concubine
桃蓮が側室であることは多くの人が知っています
Then these concubines are a bit like our current professional climbers
そうすると、この妾たちは、現在のプロの登山家に少し似ています。
In fact, he climbed and climbed for a period of time
実際、彼は一定期間登り続けました。
He closed the mountain again, and went back to his proper job
彼は再び山を閉じ、本来の仕事に戻った
Then after a while of doing proper work, I went to climb, go to work, and go to screw
それから、しばらく適当な仕事をした後、登りに行き、仕事に行き、ネジを締めに行きました
So sometimes the real men catch those
だから時々本物の男がそれらを捕まえる
Obviously know that he is a concubine
明らかに彼が側室であることを知っています
But just can't find evidence to catch him
しかし彼を捕まえる証拠が見つからない
This is like the Yi Zhimei bunny inside
これはまるでイー・ジーメイのウサギのようなものです
In fact, because I soon knew that Yi Zhimei, you are a little rabbit
実際、私はすぐにイー・ジメイが小さなウサギだと知ったので、
But just can't find evidence to catch him
しかし彼を捕まえる証拠が見つからない
Because he stole probably all
彼はおそらくすべてを盗んだから
So I won't sell or take it out
だから売れない、出さない
so hard to catch
捕まえるのがとても難しい
then this is all
それならこれですべてです
I think it's all on paper
全部紙に書いてあると思う
official articles
公式記事
what about the fact
事実はどうですか
did you fight
戦ったの？
right
右
Article Center of Peng Guo Articles
潭国記事の記事センター
In fact, we can't see it in the party
実際、パーティーでは見えません
Because in the end he ended up betting
結局彼は賭けをしてしまったからだ
Or the official said
もしくは役人が言ってた
Make up for this responsibility
この責任を埋め合わせてください
But it didn't say that the responsibility of eating is the responsibility of the component
しかし、食べる責任は成分の責任であるとは言っていない
It's usually about taking the blame
それは通常、責任を取ることについてです
Including those supplements, if he
それらのサプリメントも含めて、もし彼が
according to the law
法令に従って
If he didn't catch it at the scene
現場で捕まえられなかったら
He also wants this account to be deducted
彼はこの口座からの控除も望んでいます
But how to beat him again
しかし、彼を再び倒す方法
usually in writing
通常は書面で
we don't see what it actually means
それが実際に何を意味するのかはわかりません
so
それで
really
本当
Thanks
ありがとう
hard to decide
決めるのが難しい
because I can say anyway
とにかく言えるから
It is recommended that everyone can raise a dog yellow dog
誰でも黄色い犬を飼うことをお勧めします
Compared with my dog, it is useless to say that this kind of dog is now a pet
うちの犬と比べたらこんな犬がペットになったと言っても無駄です
My family has a Shanzi dog. The puppy stole all the downstairs and only sent it outside.
私の家族はシャンジ犬を飼っていますが、その子犬が階下のものをすべて盗んで、外に放り出しただけです。
Because it's useless, now it's a pet, not a dog imitation, it's useless at all
役に立たないから、今は犬の真似ではなくペットです、まったく役に立たない
This is the end of our lecture today, thank you very much for this wonderful lecture by Professor Wu
今日の講義はこれで終わります。呉先生の素晴らしい講義をありがとうございました。
Then the audience responded very enthusiastically, and everyone can invite him again in private
すると聴衆は非常に熱狂的に反応し、誰もが再び彼をプライベートに招待できるようになりました。
thank you all
皆さん、ありがとうございました